<xml>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q818590">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Feeding with infant formula milk power" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q818590" RELQ_USERID="U492196" RELQ_USERNAME="U492196">
<RelQSubject>a few questions?</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi I have two questions that I can't answer it myself, so I want some help from you. One is that since yesterday I started to give fruits of Buckwheat porridge and Hip today also gave a few scoops no reaction, but I'd like to put my lunch today in the mashed potatoes a little scoop of mashed potatoes Turkey (given only once and stopped him, because then he got was a cold) I can believe that Buckwheat I entered and continue with Turkey? 7 months and we're a little bit and I think He fell behind with meat purees: (<br/> My second question is this: how often can I put am Frizopep in mashed potatoes or polenta, we eat three times a day. For now I put 1 m at midday. Behind with your weight and want to breastfeed, pozahranâ as manages to suck too acidic is introduced bit by bit and can be used for the main meal or between meals only?   can I prepare Compote? The mess that has cornstarch is introduced again little by little? Oh, enough:) I'd appreciate if you help me</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818590_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U307577" RELC_USERNAME="U307577">
<RelCText>You seem pretty confused. Buckwheat is not entered for two days with the meat you I hold back nothing. You can't give 2 days buckwheat and meat immediately <br/> <br/> am you can put in all the more, the better. However, if the child is slightly acidic, it won't feed him. It's great for feeding with corn, but I'd give semolina or mess but not sour every day. Although the corn be kept allergen. <br/> <br/> will still give you a tip to finding a good children's gastroenterologist he the best answers to all your questions and will mostly give you scheme with what, how and when you've been feeding.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818590_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U492196" RELC_USERNAME="U492196">
<RelCText>[quote author = Sunshine Mom link = topic = 818590. msg29826068 # msg29826068 date = 1420451040] <br/> you seem pretty confused. Buckwheat is not entered for two days with the meat you I hold back nothing. You can't give 2 days buckwheat and meat immediately <br/> <br/> am you can put in all the more, the better. However, if the child is slightly acidic, it won't feed him. It's great for feeding with corn but I would give Gris or mash, but not sour every day. Although the corn be kept allergen. <br/> <br/> will still give you a tip to finding a good children's gastroenterologist he the best answers to all your questions and will mostly give you scheme with what, how and when you've been feeding. <br/> [/quote] I can't introduce myself one at a food? I know some mothers who didn't even introduce it give new food did not observe anything at all and some say go " him of the child something to finish " I give the paps, vegetable puree but it is tired of always the same: outtajoint: not only does, and am very confused. I bought the best hypoallergenic cauliflower puree, meat, carrot, white with green all a's but I don't know   how long does it take to bring a vegetable like? and every day to give him until he reaches a whole pot? can I give baked green pecker of sterilized jar sealing</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818590_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U307577" RELC_USERNAME="U307577">
<RelCText>You alone, but your child is allergy and you should watch. in a healthy child with one product is powered at least 4 days, and you want to give for two days two totally different food group. <br/> <br/> and don't think the baby is sick, it doesn't know the new food while his offer. It is best not to listen to other involved mothers If you don't want to bring your child's study, then wonder what to feed him at least one Lead. 4-5 days and the quantity you have entered at least 3 more days and then you can start with the new <br/> <br/> power does not need to be fast with nothing you hold back time, there is better a healthy child, you can eat all than the allergic and wonder what to give him.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818590_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U492196" RELC_USERNAME="U492196">
<RelCText>[quote author = Sunshine Mom link = topic = 818590. msg29826269 # msg29826269 date = 1420452775] <br/> yourself, but your child is allergy and you should watch. in a healthy child with one product is powered at least 4 days, and you want to give for two days two totally different food group. <br/> <br/> and don't think the baby is sick, it doesn't know the new food While he doesn't offer. It is best not to listen to other involved moms, if you don't want to bring your child's study, then wonder what to feed him at least one Lead. 4-5 days and the quantity you have entered at least 3 more days and then you can start with the new <br/> <br/> power does not need to be fast with nothing you hold back time. better a healthy child, you can eat everything, than allergic and wonder what to give him. <br/> [/quote] http://www.balevbiomarket.com/bio-pure-ot-pueshko-meso-125gr.html for a start how to give from this paste, after all meat?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818590_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U316213" RELC_USERNAME="U316213">
<RelCText>[quote author = duda212121 link = topic = 818590. msg29833759 # msg29833759 date = 1420537586] <br/> [quote author = Sunshine Mom link = topic = 818590. msg29826269 # msg29826269 date = 1420452775] <br/> yourself, but your child is allergy and you should watch. in a healthy child with one product is powered at least 4 days, and you want to give for two days two totally different food group. <br/> <br/> and don't think that baby is tired, it does not know the new food while his offer. It is best not to listen to other involved moms, if you don't want to bring your child's study, then wonder what to feed him at least one Lead. 4-5 days and the quantity you have entered at least 3 more days and then you can start with the new <br/> <br/> power does not need to be fast with nothing you hold back time. better a healthy child, you can eat everything, than allergic and wonder what to give him. <br/> [/quote] http://www.balevbiomarket.com/bio-pure-ot-pueshko-meso-125gr.html for a start how to give from this paste, after all meat? <br/> [/quote] <br/> This puree is not just meat. It is 40% meat the rest of rice and water. The mashed potatoes are divided by 2 days in a row. Given as a supplement to vegetable purees</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q818632">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Feeding with infant formula milk power" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q818632" RELQ_USERID="U436740" RELQ_USERNAME="U436740">
<RelQSubject>question about vegetable purees</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi, Mami. <br/> started to top up her daughter with vegetable purees, upon the recommendation of our pediatrician's Office gave first carrot and eat it, then gave them broccoli-frown a lot but eats 2 3 spoons. Today I tried potato because it's been 5 6 days of broccoli, but she cries and it spit out. I added and Stern, but again didn't want it so my question is tomorrow and I suggest to you to wait for potato or a couple weeks with it if you don't wants, and to OFFER you tomorrow for example, parsnip to not only feed it with carrot, I want to ask another thing-since it is breast milk, the doctor told me to 2 3 weeks to replace the lunch meal with pŝre, and the afternoon messing. But she eats 60 70 most from the jar and doesn't want more, he starts giving me signs that he wants to dosuče. Kk to replace him this meal as I think she's going to want to sukva? <br/></RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818632_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U26662" RELC_USERNAME="U26662">
<RelCText>I suggest potato, you don't want it. Why force it, it makes no sense to most disgusted and potatoes and even from solid food. You can try parsnips. <br/> Of how many months is she? Before at least year's total bullshit to step in for a meal, and by force. Each meal to godinkata should be Milky you puree, then dohranvaš with milk/am. As you enter the milk for the dairy and nutrition is considered, including cheese, butter etc But to replace meals entirely with vegetables, and two meals to replace???? Completely absurd! Now that dočetoh feed, in this case, sounds even more outrageous recommendation of the pediatrician's Office. I personally wouldn't even script exactly with the advice and on nutrition. Listen to what he has to say, but you can count and your intuition and above all of the signals that you send the child. I will paste-OK, do not force it! Life will eat solid food, there's no forever to suck her. now the basic needs is milk.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818632_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U436740" RELC_USERNAME="U436740">
<RelCText>My baby is 5 months old. Afternoon rice porridge eating it with alacrity, and according to you when to turn fruit purees? After mine all vegetable?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818632_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U26662" RELC_USERNAME="U26662">
<RelCText>There's no way to go first all vegetable, some vegetables are introduced on a much later age. Setting up say 3-4-5 the grocery store, then setting up multiple fetuses. Then grain-gluten-free, glutenovi, vegetables, fruits again again, meat, milk, egg yolk, etc how do her Rice porridge with milk, or water, how much he eats, dohranvaš.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818632_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U433791" RELC_USERNAME="U433791">
<RelCText>Hello <br/> once you have introduced two vegetables, why not combine carrot and broccoli? So it's not going to be uniform. And you can add and potato puree-you will get combined, will disguise the potato. I like cheese and IM so far that my daughter in its pure form it refuses. <br/> may want Stern and just because it is easier, if you have not created a custom to eat with a spoon. My daughter is now almost 5, but I remember how angry at first attempts with the spoon-I had a feeling that tells me-let's get nacokam with the teat, what do you do with this crap. <br/> as Stern-I'm not nursed, I had no milk, but I refused to dohranâ with breast milk. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818632_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U436740" RELC_USERNAME="U436740">
<RelCText>[quote author = vitoroga link = Mesechinka topic = 818632. msg29828286 # msg29828286 date = 1420468807] <br/> can't go first all vegetable, some vegetables are introduced on a much later age. Setting up say 3-4-5 the grocery store, then setting up multiple fetuses. Then grain-gluten-free, glutenovi, vegetables, fruits again again, meat, milk, egg yolk, etc how do her Rice porridge with milk, or water, how much he eats, dohranvaš. <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> Hello! Thanks for the tips! I tried Today with parsnip and liked it. I do oatmeal 80 and for this afternoon and come on-give to 4 and 6 to 30 and then wants to suck Even I think tomorrow and do 120-if he wants to eat is having second thoughts about fruit., but if you say that I can include them when you give them-morning or evening? Because at 12 noon and afternoon give vegetable porridge for two weeks already and make her porridge with warm water ... first time it harersa taaka and decided that then you don't have to suffer with breast milk because my already reduced a lot.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q818915">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Of the market" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q818915" RELQ_USERID="U45121" RELQ_USERNAME="U45121">
<RelQSubject>Question regarding a complaint from a type of promotional brochure</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>I know that someone familiar with the subject matter and therefore asking you! <br/> <br/> I want to write a complaint in respect of a type of promotional brochure, specifically one that is placed at the door of the dwelling (as in type is do not disturb signs hotels \ Clean). <br/> <br/> years ago a telecommunications company was placed by the doors. We had attempted robbery immediately afterwards, as the lock was camouflaged with a brochure. After a while the same telecommunications company has released such brochures again. Then I contacted them directly and explained to them what to use their ad, that's not the way we got to mailboxes they put there as others or glued posters. I thought I knew until yesterday-the same type of advertising. This time, I wish to make a formal complaint. Please give advice to whom and where! <br/></RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818915_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U45121" RELC_USERNAME="U45121">
<RelCText>Does anyone have an idea where this type of complaint is submitted. newsm78</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818915_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U386556" RELC_USERNAME="U386556">
<RelCText>I have no idea. I have just proposed. To leave a written request to the Office of the company and to insist to get your answer in what period would you answer written naturally, to take further actions, etc. If necessary, etc., can and the station management with incoming number.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818915_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U190567" RELC_USERNAME="U190567">
<RelCText>I think we need to discuss with neighbours <br/> entry of foreign people in the entrance. Though some   has opened the door. <br/> can and a personal meeting with the PR, be prepared with a written complaint, <br/> to pass. <br/> " have the same motion and " " from the " catalog, Nikea hang on the doors, but in this moment <br/> was driving home, I asked the guy why-so I'm told. <br/> Know that there are practices in other countries outside the door to leave the bottle <br/> with milk, but with us ... .... It's just a sign of the robbers <br/> write about success and development.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818915_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U457613" RELC_USERNAME="U457613">
<RelCText>Turn to the Commission for the protection of consumers. They control the return messages.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q818915_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U7954" RELC_USERNAME="U7954">
<RelCText>I can't got what sign of the thieves? They <br/> thieves if you so want to hide nabeza, will bring some spamče to put him on a two door ... <br/> exactly really think about access in the entrance you ... <br/> <br/> what should I say " motion "? " " obviously, Nikea Ikea?!?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q819304">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Engagement and wedding" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q819304" RELQ_USERID="U416599" RELQ_USERNAME="U416599">
<RelQSubject>Question?????</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi, I didn't know exactly which group to ask the question, and I apologize. At the end of the month I'm getting married, but we have a child before marriage. And I question whether we should change then his birth certificate with my new last name? Due to the bad weather I can't get out to go to the Office to ask and eager to fill in the question you ask. <br/> <br/> good day:))))))</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819304_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U427474" RELC_USERNAME="U427474">
<RelCText>[quote author = gostenkata75 link = topic = 819304. msg29856336 # msg29856336 date = 1420782536] <br/> Hi, I didn't know exactly which group to ask the question, and I apologize. At the end of the month I'm getting married, but we have a child before marriage. And I question whether we should change then his birth certificate with my new last name? Due to the bad weather I can't get out to go to the Office to ask and eager to fill in the question you ask. <br/> <br/> good day:)))))) <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> as far as I'm aware the data recorded on the birth certificate be changed only by a court decision  ;-) <br/> wouldn't it follow that it brings this family generally, if pripoznato of your future spouse?   newsm78</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819304_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U416599" RELC_USERNAME="U416599">
<RelCText>Yes, with the father's last name is. But mine is written there with my maiden name and wondering whether we should change the Act with my new family. Thanks anyway:)</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819304_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U427474" RELC_USERNAME="U427474">
<RelCText>[quote author = gostenkata75 link = topic = 819304. msg29856549 # msg29856549 date = 1420786528] <br/> To, with the father's last name is. But mine is written there with my maiden name and wondering whether we should change the Act with my new family. Thanks anyway:) <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> written So it sounded like the name of the child  : lol: <br/> according to me-no, birth certificate data to reflect that point. <br/> at that time you have been with this family  )</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819304_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U365644" RELC_USERNAME="U365644">
<RelCText>Birth certificate does not change as the identity card. If the mother was married and divorced several times, all acts of the children you will be rereleasing? <br/> Act remains as.:p: eace</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819304_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U416599" RELC_USERNAME="U416599">
<RelCText>Âsnoo, thank you. I apologize for the incorrect assigned me a question, with a small child around me I entered clearly thought:)   newsm78</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q819531">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Of the market" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q819531" RELQ_USERID="U2307" RELQ_USERNAME="U2307">
<RelQSubject>Quick questions for children's gift</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Any feedback for NERF? <br/> <br/> [img width = 600 height = 311] http://www.hippoland.net/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/a/4/a48872840_653569895930_main_13_2_.jpg [/img] <br/> <br/> I have no occasion for gift. A friend said that it will appeal. Doesn't hurt if they hit  : hahaha: <br/> cars and guns, if I have to buy a ton of.</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819531_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U8585" RELC_USERNAME="U8585">
<RelCText>Congratulations for the idea about the topic! <br/> <br/> this gun very thought Christmas gift for a child to friends, but I didn't dare to take. Otherwise, you may have cut it by listening to ads on children's television.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819531_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U157065" RELC_USERNAME="U157065">
<RelCText>Nice theme, the more that I have to think about children's gift <br/> someone to say a couple of words about the game Dino " " bite? I ordered it for my daughter by the reduction of Komsed this week as a slightly belated Christmas gift. Would the idea that   houses often gather children and at least to play together instead of fighting. But now I wonder if they'd like. The fence between it and one with a rabbit, but as you know the stuff, there will be a perpetual dispute who caught the rabbit and why exactly it ... <br/> waiting for More Komsed to de and to confirm the order, but that's another story. <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819531_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U49314" RELC_USERNAME="U49314">
<RelCText>Nerf weapon. <br/> This is our model and consider it a suitable toy. <br/> <br/> [img width = 600 height = 211] http://www.hippoland.net/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/5/6/56617.jpg [/img] <br/> <br/> Extra bullets from Jumbo, because they were two or three times cheaper. <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819531_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U144390" RELC_USERNAME="U144390">
<RelCText>Girls, can anyone tell me whether in the store in Plovdiv, the reduction of Komsed is still in force-I was looking at the site and there is no longer any announced promotion and prices are standard, but I was wondering if the store at least I won't be able to catch reduction. as I recall, mentioned the reduction of the 5th to the 10th of January. <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819531_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U287795" RELC_USERNAME="U287795">
<RelCText>Hello, one very quick question I have. I'm trying to order from komsed. No registration, I picked the product, wrote her name and address, Tel. then complete the order. There was no sign that I ordered and in e-mail. If I ordered at all??? how much is delivery? I searched but found nothing. I don't like their site. :(<br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q819996">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Nursery and gardens" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q819996" RELQ_USERID="U24513" RELQ_USERNAME="U24513">
<RelQSubject>About immunisation prizapisvane a child lived abroad in BG Manger?</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi cheats! <br/> friend comes to visit from Germany for a few months in Bulgaria and wants to release the child to the nursery. In the city there is room in the crib and it is not a problem to accept her, but wanting and document the child's immunisation. <br/> she has them. a passport from Germany, but it turns out that their vaccines do not correspond with our and the Manger are not faced with a similar case and don't know what to say?!  : shock: <br/> child was born there, but there's a BG birth certificate and SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER. <br/> If anyone knows how this works with children who have lived abroad and immunized, and are adopting in the nursery or kindergarten in BG, please share? </RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819996_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U47989" RELC_USERNAME="U47989">
<RelCText>You need to find the child's pediatrician and he to write in the file, that the child has all the immunizations for her age. The only difference of this age is that BCG is not in Germany, and in the BG is placed in the maternity ward. Vaccines in Germany are over, so no problem. BCG will most likely offer her to put when I put on the calendar of the age in the BG.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819996_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U45075" RELC_USERNAME="U45075">
<RelCText>When you save a child in KINDERGARTEN, DG or âasla are a bunch of research and a note from a pediatrician with immunisation. It is best, after will stay here as long to find the child's pediatrician, who can issue a note with care and immunizations, as well as made the necessary examinations for parasites, blood, etc.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819996_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U24513" RELC_USERNAME="U24513">
<RelCText>All studies have been made on the basis of them the doctor issued a note saying the child is healthy, but carried out document immunizations, not give, because I still have not been carried out by the same doctor.   <br/> copy of immunization Passport told us to apply, but are not sure whether the crib in the inspection bodies to make them no problem, that's why I'm asking if there is anyone with such a case to share how they procedirali. :hug:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819996_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U47989" RELC_USERNAME="U47989">
<RelCText>Well, if you change a fag here, you still wouldn't have been carried out by the same:) I already told you how our procediraše doctor and we've never had a problem with the garden. The transcript with the dates of the German vaccines immunization records in English. I gave her a copy of their German. cardboard, as well as a printout which is what vaccine Bcg-it does not. I like to put it, until it became the 7 d for PPD.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q819996_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U24513" RELC_USERNAME="U24513">
<RelCText>Many thanks for your replies! Already the year Baby Crib  :D</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q820207">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Feeding with infant formula milk power" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q820207" RELQ_USERID="U134442" RELQ_USERNAME="U134442">
<RelQSubject>Question about introduction of mash</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>My son is 6 months. Of the month give vegetable purees and now I would like to open up his oatmeal Nutritional regime. is as follows: <br/> 8:00 am 200 ml <br/> 11:30 vegetable purees 130 d <br/> 15:00 am 200 ml <br/> 18:30 am 200 ml <br/> 21:30 am 200 ml <br/> Feeding at 6:30 you have to replace with the mess?   What is the amount you need to reach? 150 ml? On days when I don't give a damn mess, am I give you about nutrition? Fruit purees don't give more.</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q820207_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U307577" RELC_USERNAME="U307577">
<RelCText>The mess you can give her at 18.30, but if you're replacing a meal milk quantity is the baby asked,150 is OK, why there are days that will not eat gruel?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q820207_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U134442" RELC_USERNAME="U134442">
<RelCText>Because a lot of pumping the shit and they told me to alternate with fruit puree, which I still don't give a fuck.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q820207_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U307577" RELC_USERNAME="U307577">
<RelCText>It's nonsense for pumping. There is no such thing. : naughty: Fruit puree is not eating and not alternate with mash and mash or in between feeding my daughter eats porridge each day, and sometimes twice as my milk teeth is due. inflated. :p: eace <br/> <br/> Ask the one who told you to brought fruit puree with mess, whether it feeds on fruits of the main meal.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q820207_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U12356" RELC_USERNAME="U12356">
<RelCText>Yes, at 18.30 with a milk substitute gruel. As soon as the child can take. <br/> with pumping is ridiculous, there is no such thing  : naughty: my son loves kašički and eating a lot and all. Well .... is not modified:-) Fruit puree is basically not eatable, they told you already.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q820207_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U447159" RELC_USERNAME="U447159">
<RelCText>The best, in my opinion, set any fruit puree and then mix with the cream of wheat. My boy loves it. Give the porridge or the morning or evening, judge alone. I gave her in the morning with this in mind that I was going to fill in for breakfast at 10 a.m. He used for breakfast and now 8 months. eating poparka no problem, at lunch and in the evening the puree to 18 h. will replace with milk porridge. For pumping I can't say we're thick without the mess and trouble.  : hahaha:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q820710">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Housing and property" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q820710" RELQ_USERID="U200332" RELQ_USERNAME="U200332">
<RelQSubject>Question about municipal housing????</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi I want to ask if a familiar single father and dvetemu girls was given municipal housing, apartment takes you if one girl get married?</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q820710_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U55567" RELC_USERNAME="U55567">
<RelCText>You will need to move to less as quadrature, in accordance with the Ordinance. Depends on the municipality, it may take years, as you decide. He's not going to take it, quietly.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q820710_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U200332" RELC_USERNAME="U200332">
<RelCText>The problem is that the apartment is a major overhaul and they don't want to move. <br/> one girl was going to do a wedding, but I will postpone <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q820710_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U55567" RELC_USERNAME="U55567">
<RelCText>If anyone has his eye on the flat pressed him to move, there are standards in the Ordinance. But sooner or later, these daughters will get married-or should I stay with him at least to live/documents/or to submit an application for buy.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q820710_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U162639" RELC_USERNAME="U162639">
<RelCText>What is the apartment? How big are the children listed in the accomodation.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q820710_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U200332" RELC_USERNAME="U200332">
<RelCText>Hi! <br/> housing is medium. Children are the years. 22.24 <br/> Entered are in the order <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q821052">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Children's health" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q821052" RELQ_USERID="U42209" RELQ_USERNAME="U42209">
<RelQSubject>Question about the vaccine against cervical cancer</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi <br/> want to immunize my daughter which is the exact age at the time. Since before placing the Cervarix vaccine have read that you should consult her doctor recommend me clinic in Sofia where we can do this and set it up? Thanks <br/> <br/> Greetings <br/></RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q821052_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U300647" RELC_USERNAME="U300647">
<RelCText>Should contact their GP. I'm should inoculate her daughter. Success!</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q821052_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U42209" RELC_USERNAME="U42209">
<RelCText>My daughter lives in Botevgrad, and there are like doctors in the 18th century people tired of incompetence, including my father. I want a good specialist in order to no complications and side effects-to examine whether the fine is appropriate.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q821052_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U223700" RELC_USERNAME="U223700">
<RelCText>Coordinates of the onkoginekolozi checked outlet, please <br/> <br/> Coordinates of doctors: <br/>-ass. Popova, 02/831 7671-review, conization, Surgery/Gynaecology Clinic filed a fifth city hospital/<br/> <br/>    -Dr. Darkwa, GSM: 0888 318 967, Tel. 02/971 4898, ext. 31 for review, biopsy <br/>    -Dr. Dale, GSM: 0888 754 077, UL. Pop bogomil 23, Tel. 02 983 64 06 and Cellphone. wire. 0888754077/after 14 hours of recording hours/<br/> <br/>  -  ass. Dr. Tsvetanka Damn k. M. H., obstetrician-gynecologist oncologist, surgeon, Tel: 02/873 2273 and 0888/661 543, e-mail: tzv.dyankova@mail.bg <br/> <br/> Dr. Bozhidar slavchev, g. Sofia, Strelbishte, " " str. " 6, " Kostina Tel. 02/02/408 1843, 859 6071, GSM +/654 925 <br/> <br/>  -Prof. Dangi-review in Tokuda Monday and Thursday, Tel. the front desk 02/403 49 28 (must be booked at the reception desk) <br/> <br/>    -Dr. Krassimir Dantas, obstetrician-gynecologist, an oncologist and Chief of operative Gynecology ward at " " 1 " AG " Sveta Sofia, GSM: 0888/639 061, Tel. in the private office: 02/858.9024 <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q821052_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U42209" RELC_USERNAME="U42209">
<RelCText>Thanks so much for the comprehensive response!!!!</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q821052_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U300647" RELC_USERNAME="U300647">
<RelCText>Wow, Nefertarri, my admiration! Will make these useful coordinates!  : bouquet:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q821702">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Of the market" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q821702" RELQ_USERID="U73708" RELQ_USERNAME="U73708">
<RelQSubject>Question for the buggy?</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi! I apologize if the topic is not here, please be moved, but I did not know where to ask. My question is whether this really becomes a stroller for a newborn-URhttp://www.bambino.bg/cosatto-detska-kolichka-cosatto-supa-cuddle-monster-p-9891.html. Live I haven't seen her, because the town where I live there are no such trolleys. Life and health wait baby at the beginning of February and I'm wondering if this model is suitable for a little baby. Basically I figured to compound the carriages, but this much I liked, as far as I know the brand is nice. A few years ago with my daughter used stroller Kangaro Carrera, but I'm not very happy with the brand. I would be happy to share some reviews and recommendations for a decent shopping cart of not very high price! Thanks in advance!:   bouquet:</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q821702_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U455014" RELC_USERNAME="U455014">
<RelCText>I personally would not put a newborn in a basket:p: my   eace is combined and now use the winter (baby) basket </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q821702_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U26662" RELC_USERNAME="U26662">
<RelCText>I've never seen it, but I don't think it is for a newborn. At least I can't see the body turning towards the mother and baby, at least in my opinion, this is an absolute must. <br/> pp stroller isn't exactly a cart without a separate baskets, i.e. one in which the body is transformed from a baby in the seat for the older child.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q821702_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U455014" RELC_USERNAME="U455014">
<RelCText>In my opinion these are combined with separate bins give for example our  :p: eace <br/> [spoiler] http://bebemax.eu/index.php? section = ITM &amp; itemid = 1373 [/spoiler] <br/> [b] <br/> Mesechinka vitoroga [/b] is absolutely right for directions to the mother. Not to mention that the baby should lie, and I don't see how a newborn will be comfortable in this cage.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q821702_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U262213" RELC_USERNAME="U262213">
<RelCText>I've seen the cart-in my opinion, this is not a stroller for a newborn.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q821702_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U26662" RELC_USERNAME="U26662">
<RelCText>Yes, NikoStorm, you're right. In the end it turns out that the stroller is a stroller with a few baskets for newborn, seat for the older child, etc., no matter whether they are physically different bins or one that is transformed. I was really interesting and I've done some homework, because and my Kangaroo Victoria waters combined. This maybe a little, but since I asked the question, so now you're responding: lol:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q822837">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Expectant mothers" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q822837" RELQ_USERID="U453440" RELQ_USERNAME="U453440">
<RelQSubject>important question!</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>The mothers, a few days ago I had sex with my girlfriend, but without a condom. Now suspects that they may be pregnant. Constantly says that's bad. Even puke and she had a temperature. <br/> my question is whether the pregnancy test will show something at this early stage? I can't wait until her came. <br/> give me some advice please.</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q822837_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U10569" RELC_USERNAME="U10569">
<RelCText>Highly doubt that sickens me and the temperature to be a sign of pregnancy right at this stage. That does not rule out the possibility is really pregnant <br/> to doesn't make you a crazy Ladybug every month, young man, you don't risk more to have sex without protection. It's not fair to the girl, and for yourself. <br/> bored-life father.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q822837_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U436333" RELC_USERNAME="U436333">
<RelCText>It is not clear exactly how many days ago, this happened. Test reports to the third day somewhere, but if you had doubts had up to 72 hours of the accident, your partner to take 1 tablet Eskapele</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q822837_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U460161" RELC_USERNAME="U460161">
<RelCText>The test is done after a delay. Otherwise you risk incorrect result. There's no way to find out with a magic wand, and so waiting. I think your friend was worried that the described symptoms are from stress. If you get away with it, next time don't do shit. There are pills, condoms, etc. ...: xarms:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q822837_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U10569" RELC_USERNAME="U10569">
<RelCText>Eskapel are not candy with a magical action. So will &#1117; mixed hormones that ... <br/> Let me squirm a bit, daylights and learn to be more responsible for their own health. <br/> big people.  :p: eace</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q822837_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U229123" RELC_USERNAME="U229123">
<RelCText>These are symptoms of the flu, and by the way  :p eace: you'll have to wait for the delay.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q823027">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Risk pregnancy" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q823027" RELQ_USERID="U499615" RELQ_USERNAME="U499615">
<RelQSubject>An important issue for folic acid and vitamins during pregnancy</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>I want to ask you ... ... ... ... Is it normal to not be discharged but only folic acid vitamins???? I live in Bulgaria, I'm pregnant in the 3gs and say: will they go when there are 10gs what to see! In my previous pregnancy drinking folic acid  , but lost the fetus. So I wanted to know is it normal ever to you such a thing?</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q823027_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U500341" RELC_USERNAME="U500341">
<RelCText>Some compound " " contain vitamins and folic acid are exactly balanced by certain trace elements. In my " have folic acid in the form of l-methyl folate 400mkg " and that was the reason to stop the use of Neofolik. What exactly is important include your medication.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q823027_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U41367" RELC_USERNAME="U41367">
<RelCText>Vitamins are hardly without folic. Read their content. Does not prevent you to drink extra just for the reviews themselves folic is normal.   heartbeat will be jammed even at 7 with Ma, but abroad they look at more of the rare  :D</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q823027_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U440360" RELC_USERNAME="U440360">
<RelCText>3. is one week before the estimated date of next menstruation. There must be some mistake.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q823027_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U443977" RELC_USERNAME="U443977">
<RelCText>  I think there does not look to us as the weeks, from fertilisation.  : roll: This means five years with at least I think so I  :p: eace</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q823027_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U64047" RELC_USERNAME="U64047">
<RelCText>Watch nowhere weeks differently. The author probably count them. <br/> But abroad they don't count unless you're pregnant last 10-12 years, as read. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q823489">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Family relationships" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q823489" RELQ_USERID="U245236" RELQ_USERNAME="U245236">
<RelQSubject>Questions about donation</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi <br/> would be enough, if you find the answers to your questions here. I know I need to consult with a lawyer, but at the time I was totally impossible. <br/> <br/> Parents donate two children with equal parts real estate. One child rest before his parents and leaves only as heir husband <br/> can parents to request annulment of the donation as their deceased child is not left descendants descendants? <br/> what portion of donations of property will inherit a wife? <br/> If the donation is revoked, upon the death of the parents, can the other child to claim the property of deceased as to this point, it's going to be the only survivor child and maybe (I think) all parts are reserved for him? <br/></RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q823489_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U263477" RELC_USERNAME="U263477">
<RelCText>As far as I am aware, when the property was inherited through a donation, not husband succeeded him. <br/> according to art. 20 of the family code, the rights stuff on them and cash deposits, acquired during the marriage by inheritance or donation, belong to this family who has acquired  :p: eace <br/> when parents die, the successor remains only one child and can claim the property <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q823489_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U118551" RELC_USERNAME="U118551">
<RelCText>    Parents cannot cancel your donation. It is repealed only under the conditions specified are definition in art. 227 of the law on obligations and contracts. <br/>     Brother/sister of the deceased may challenge the donation after the death of his parents, but do not have chances to win, because it has not dented their part-they have equivalent property, again by donation. <br/>     descendants of the deceased child's parents and her husband. If at the date of death have been more than 10 years from the conclusion of the marriage, the husband gets 2/3 of the estate (all that has been the property of the deceased, including a donation), if it hasn't been 10 years-husband gets 1/2 of the inheritance. The rest is inherited from the parents.      </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q823489_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U245236" RELC_USERNAME="U245236">
<RelCText>Thank you all for the replies! <br/> <br/> [quote author = gathering link = topic = 823489. msg30044366 # msg30044366 date = 1422874451] <br/> After a person's death, the estate is formed by all the assets of the person and personal property, and therefore of his stock in the SIO (in practice with his death becomes SIO equity while there is marriage and husband alive she is bezdâlova) <br/> [/quote] <br/> [b] [/b] gathering , I don't understand what you mean with that. I know that the donation is an individual property and is not part of SIO. How is inherited after death, what part of the husband's property donations work? <br/> <br/> and ask what's the way donated property to be SIO? Can the other spouse to purchase it whole and thus both spouses to own it equally?   newsm78</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q823489_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U118551" RELC_USERNAME="U118551">
<RelCText>[quote author = maslenka link = topic = 823489. msg30069657 # msg30069657 date = 1423125388] <br/> thanks for all the replies! <br/> [b] [/b] gathering, I don't understand what you mean with that. I know that the donation is an individual property and is not part of SIO. How is inherited after death, what part of the husband's property donations work? <br/> <br/> and ask what's the way donated property to be SIO? Can the other spouse to purchase it whole and thus both spouses equally to own it?   newsm78 <br/> [/quote] <br/> on the first question I answered above, when the family has no children. If the husband inherits personal property with children-divide it equally. <br/> <br/> If I have property personal property, I can sell it to her husband. If the sale put family funds, will become SIO. If my husband bought it entirely with private funds, might one day challenge that the property is SIO and get it all over and I was left without anything (actually, I do not believe that in such deals will pay the spouses property to each other). But in this insanely exercise I don't see any point. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q823489_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U245236" RELC_USERNAME="U245236">
<RelCText>Thank you, Hermione, again for the reply  : hug: <br/> For sale realized, let me ask about the other option-donation. <br/> take the following completely hypothetical situation: <br/> man and woman in marriage, with a minor child. The woman has donated property. If the woman donated half the property of her husband, and both will have it equally. After a while, your donation can be challenged only by the child (or newsm78). But in this case it is not so important. My point is that at the time of the donation, are not impaired preserved parts of the heirs, right? <br/> suppose that coincidentally the woman and child rest. The proportion of a woman inherits from her husband and from her parents (or siblings), right? If half of the property was not bestowed on her husband, then her relatives would receive a larger part, right? Can they then to challenge for impaired reserved parts, since the death of the woman, they are survivors, and real at the time of the donation were not such? <br/> again, it's completely hypothetical, I just want to clear some things up.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q826529">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Of time abroad" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q826529" RELQ_USERID="U502377" RELQ_USERNAME="U502377">
<RelQSubject>Question of Uizer ticket Reservation is payment?</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Question to the educated <br/> <br/> can reserve a ticket for free travel to be paid and if so-what the deadline for payment is </RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q826529_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U37576" RELC_USERNAME="U37576">
<RelCText>Hello, <br/> Regularly fly with this company and purchase the tickets through the Internet. It's not my impression there is an option to " booking ", without payment. The moment you fill in all the data edinstvenstvenata option is to push the " purchase ". Minute then receive " SMS " for iz″ršenoto payment. <br/> I hope I was helpful.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q826529_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U13339" RELC_USERNAME="U13339">
<RelCText>[b] I WOULD LIKE (a) to PAY THEIR FARE by BANK TRANSFER. WHEN DO I HAVE TO TRANSLATE THE AMOUNT? [/b] <br/> <br/> payment must be completed within 24 hours from the creation of the reservation. The confirmation of the reservation can take up to 4-5 business days.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q826529_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U40015" RELC_USERNAME="U40015">
<RelCText>You can make a reservation for 24 hours just by specifying the payment by bank transfer, but there should be some time until the date of the flight, I think about 20 days required at least.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q826529_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U422287" RELC_USERNAME="U422287">
<RelCText>If you reserve on Friday can pay Monday.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q826529_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U164150" RELC_USERNAME="U164150">
<RelCText>Experience has shown that when paying by bank transfer can be slow for at least 2 days. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q827854">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Expectant mothers" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q827854" RELQ_USERID="U396779" RELQ_USERNAME="U396779">
<RelQSubject>A question about operation</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>After " get "   in   in sredeta 9 month of March   allowed to pick a date for the birth with the surgery, do I have to wait for the term date and what effect the baby?</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q827854_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U126111" RELC_USERNAME="U126111">
<RelCText>As close as the operation will be close to term. Unless you have medical reasons, of course.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q827854_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U502615" RELC_USERNAME="U502615">
<RelCText>If everything is OK with you and the baby can you pick which date you want, but we recommend at least 2 weeks to take her-9</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q827854_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U229822" RELC_USERNAME="U229822">
<RelCText>To me my doctor determined them. Both strove to be ten days before term.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q827854_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U501254" RELC_USERNAME="U501254">
<RelCText>I as far as I know, a c-section is done 10 days before the term unless it is urgent as nine days after term. But I guess it could be anywhere and the date, but it must be somewhere around 10-15 days before term.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q827854_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U502640" RELC_USERNAME="U502640">
<RelCText>Hi included the topic:) I'll bear me a c-section and was a little afraid of the operation and the date I chose her and is 10 days prior to the term me:) </RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q828262">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Engagement and wedding" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q828262" RELQ_USERID="U452765" RELQ_USERNAME="U452765">
<RelQSubject>Question about marriage</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hello, I would like to ask you, since I'm four months of a new job and only this month I found out I was pregnant, the employer shall immediately appoint me a contract of employment, but I provide 8ch.na 470lv, I would like to ask you I I parallel, let me provide another place I take more leave and I know two months to go to hospital if I'm gone 6mes.izpitatelen period.</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q828262_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U457808" RELC_USERNAME="U457808">
<RelCText>for maintaining the date 2 ID cards or copies of them, and the fee for the 6lv civil marriage will need personal cards   of the groomsmen, and you must have a medical  :p eace: witness to the civil marriage the only condition is to be 18, I think it's a problem related to your best man, so what are these works for the maid of honor  : 35 : can you, if you need help on something, but for the marriage there must be compulsory only grooms and groomsmen  : whistle: for the implementation of the civil marriage also is paid a certain amount, but it varies and depends on many things.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q828262_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U452765" RELC_USERNAME="U452765">
<RelCText>We just want to be close but I can not choose the groomsmen and best man is his brother but for Kuma I can't select something supposed to be family or not necessarily so well, I had read in the net that I have a bridesmaid. I think that we don't want a big ceremony to sign for quite a long time and finally we decided already. What documents may to the facility in tubdispansera'm not really honestly. Thanks for rapid response</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q828262_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U457808" RELC_USERNAME="U457808">
<RelCText>[quote author = bebetors link = topic = 828262. msg30172614 # msg30172614 date = 1424189912] <br/> we just want to be close but I can not choose the groomsmen and best man is his brother but for Kuma I can't select something supposed to be family or not necessarily so well, I had read in the net that I have a bridesmaid. I think that we don't want a big ceremony to sign for quite a long time and finally we decided already. What documents May to the facility in the tubdispansera I'm not very familiar with frankly. Thanks for the rapid reply <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> is not necessarily a family, our future sponsors don't even know yet, because the sponsor lives abroad. Well or in the GP must go and he explained to you or there are private clinics, which is more expensive, but it's a lot faster. I don't know what exactly, because I just include the   to me: lol: when I go in to save civil there will satisfy you, if you have any questions, don't worry   8)</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q828262_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U493092" RELC_USERNAME="U493092">
<RelCText>And in my opinion should not be izsikva to have a maid of honor, that you judge. No problem his brother's best man and Maid of honor a friend of yours (not necessarily a couple or family) <br/> medically needed and Wasserman-go to your doctor and say you need a medical for the marriage and it will tell you where and who to go to, as for copper. from psych ward that is different in each municipality, somewhere else they want. The price for the civil marriage again is different depending on the day, obŝianata etc. <br/> I wish you a happy married life! <br/> <br/> p.s. While I wrote you already responded and a little, but we're retiling niŝk  :p eace:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q828262_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U439711" RELC_USERNAME="U439711">
<RelCText>Here we have the necessary information on many of the issues http://www.sofia-svatbi.info/</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q829007">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Business, work, professions" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q829007" RELQ_USERID="U461848" RELQ_USERNAME="U461848">
<RelQSubject>Question about post " " educator elementary school.</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi! <br/> <br/> I would like to ask you whether you know what professional qualifications should be the person who occupies the post of Counselor " "? You must have completed primary school pedagogy? <br/> <br/> greetings <br/> Sissy</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q829007_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U26740" RELC_USERNAME="U26740">
<RelCText>Elementary school pedagogy, if there are no takers for the place, then may appoint another candidate and pedagogical education.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q829007_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U461848" RELC_USERNAME="U461848">
<RelCText>[quote author = wiwi link = topic = 829007. msg30207894 # msg30207894 date = 1424550068] <br/> primary school pedagogy, if there are no takers for the place, then may appoint another candidate and pedagogical education. <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> <br/> Wiwi, thanks! <br/> <br/> I ask because I have other pedagogical education, and work in its early stages.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q829007_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U26740" RELC_USERNAME="U26740">
<RelCText>Prekvalificiraj, I did so much more enjoyable to work in its early stages. Success!</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q829007_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U461848" RELC_USERNAME="U461848">
<RelCText>[quote author = wiwi link = topic = 829007. msg30211028 # msg30211028 date = 1424608334] <br/> Prekvalificiraj, I did so much more enjoyable to work in its early stages. Good luck! <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> Retraining my starting in September, and so far I have to work. It is very difficult.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q829007_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U182627" RELC_USERNAME="U182627">
<RelCText>I am also a graduate degree with a pedagogical focus, but for 7-12 grade. I tried several times to apply for primary schools, but it is absurd, they want their elementary education and rightly so, that I was going to write a master's in elementary education. How are prekvalificirahte?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q829701">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Beautiful mom" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q829701" RELQ_USERID="U461426" RELQ_USERNAME="U461426">
<RelQSubject>Question about hair and hair-cutting</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi <br/> I've decided to go a little longer hair and it formed as a so-called " me bun ", here's the word: <br/> http://i.ytimg.com/vi/1Wu5s_VO5i0/maxresdefault.jpg <br/> <br/> http://scontent-b.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xfa1/t51.2885-15/10844096_837923322930904_1693230293_n.jpg <br/> <br/> by my calculations I need around 15-16 cm. for this purpose, my hair is currently around 9-10 as was postrigvana several times. My question is how often should her haircut, and I can make it this length without visiting the hairdresser, what danger of damage, blooms, etc. so far, I've always been a typical male hair style " type short ", and I'm not much into these things. <br/> I'd appreciate it if you help:)</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q829701_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U400915" RELC_USERNAME="U400915">
<RelCText>Very fun for me the seriousness and almost scientific interest, with that kind of attitude to the subject. : thinking::D <br/> So I can not try as much as possible to answer: <br/> "-how often do you cut it? "-depends on how much your hair grows a month <br/>-" can I get this length without visiting the hairdresser? "-hair has the strange property to grow roughly evenly on the entire chapter, not just where you want it most. If you like from both sides, to keep the hair short like the picture, until on the Crown grows long, you will need to visit your hairdresser to just at least podk″sâva/countries. <br/> "-what the danger of damage, if it blooms just leave to grow "-so don't worry); advertising industry spewing out TV spots with unhappy girls, pros″lzeni the kind of rugged, metlo-like hair apparently has reached you (long tentacles far beyond its direct target group). A healthy, with normal dense hair, long hair mainly on the Crown  : mrgreen:,   can be 5 cm without c″vne and tie. However, if she dye your hair, Perm your hair/face press, using very strong and stilizanti drying (picking up her ' ' comb for example) could have happened. <br/> If all this still relieves you, just otsipi of the mask/balm/mom and girlfriend Kudos at length:) <br/> <br/> slightly my šegovitiât I hope and informative-an introductory, in the recesses of the growth of hair, post not offended, because I really didn't have a goal! She smiled at me, that is:) <br/> P.S.: and show a picture of the result then  :D:p eace:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q829701_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U20058" RELC_USERNAME="U20058">
<RelCText>Quite a bit more length you will need for the bangs to go back and enter the queue. There is an interim period until he grows up, bangs a little bad, you may need to wear a tiara like footballers. <br/> buy from pharmacy quinine water and shampoo hininov, Bulgarian products are not expensive and act according to package directions.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q829701_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U461426" RELC_USERNAME="U461426">
<RelCText>I'm basically in this period, and this hininov shampoo and water better than the promoter under ikarov?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q829701_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U20058" RELC_USERNAME="U20058">
<RelCText>One thing to do with the other. I even help-hininovite products make hair grow faster, and because it is hair stimulant oil strengthens and protects from fatigue, which can be obtained from the force crossing over.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q829701_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U461426" RELC_USERNAME="U461426">
<RelCText>Thanks, I'm going to try, otherwise as a brand to which to navigate.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q830933">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Children's holidays, and birthdays" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q830933" RELQ_USERID="U254201" RELQ_USERNAME="U254201">
<RelQSubject>Question for the cardboard cake</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi <br/> <br/> some time ago in one of the topics discussed here the cardboard cake. I would like to ask where in Sofia or the Internet could order such a cake? Unfortunately I can not do anything alone. I would like also to know whether individual pieces of cake boxes/fold, i.e. If I could make them flat to carry them on a plane or it would screw up cut boxes. <br/> <br/> Thanks in advance!</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q830933_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U21110" RELC_USERNAME="U21110">
<RelCText>Hi, I don't know if that's what you mean: <br/> [url = http://krokotak.com/2010/11/torta-s-iznenadi/] http://krokotak.com/2010/11/torta-s-iznenadi/[/url] <br/> but if it does not take much time and great skill to make. You can print out and cut out the pieces and fold them and fill as you need them. I hope I have been helpful.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q830933_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U254201" RELC_USERNAME="U254201">
<RelCText>Yes, I mean such a cake. I managed to do something neat-as says my home ' mom ' good that you don't have to be living with their hands that will starve ' '. This sums up my skills of cutting, gluing, packing and other such activities. <br/>: 35: <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q830933_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U1343" RELC_USERNAME="U1343">
<RelCText>[quote author = Nedinka link = topic = 830933. msg30290275 # msg30290275 date = 1425500997] <br/> Hi <br/> <br/> some time ago in one of the topics discussed here the cardboard cake. [/quote] <br/> <br/> Hello, the topic is here [url = http://www.bg-mamma.com/index.php? = topicrefid 604992.0; topic = 19] this [/url]. Making a cake is not difficult, but it requires time and patience, I don't know if it could be done flat, though the idea is to have boxes. I don't know where I will wear them on the plane, but it is possible there on site to sell similar boxes and use them to assemble your cake. <br/> here any http://www.amazon.com/Birthday-Cake-Slice-Treat-Boxes/dp/B0028FIU7A/ref = sr_1_11? = s arts-crafts &amp; ie = UTF8 &amp; qid = 1425529611 &amp; sr = 1-11 &amp; keywords = paper + cake + boxes <br/> and this http://www.ebay.com/itm/3-Tier-Cake-Slice-Centerpiece-Favor-Boxes-Package-of-36-Cake-Boxes-Wedding-/261461422300? pt = LH_DefaultDomain_0 &amp; var = &amp; hash = item3ce050b0dc <br/> <br/> though that I've always made, but starting a month before the event:p: eace <br/> <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q830933_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U254201" RELC_USERNAME="U254201">
<RelCText>In Belgium want to take-two and a half hours by plane. In the Amazon I haven't seen, we looked at, but there are no similar cakes distributed-in crib and nursery schools are authorised genuine cakes and such wear. I need to put a little present in each box for each gostenče-here is a tradition and her children know that at the end of the birthday party will gain something. <br/> <br/> I'd probably have to start three months before the event:) <br/> <br/> thanks, Nancy! I will discuss the topic and I will decide-hem I wish something like that, because it is different and it's clear that he wants a lot of time, and the result for me would be pretty questionable. But it can't hurt to try.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q830933_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U1343" RELC_USERNAME="U1343">
<RelCText>Nedinka, try to look at the shops, wedding sites, the great probability is something to pop up if you ask like wedding cake slice boxes criteria  :p: eace <br/> <br/> Will handle it, I'm sure: hug:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q831179">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Housing and property" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q831179" RELQ_USERID="U505565" RELQ_USERNAME="U505565">
<RelQSubject>About directory listing</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi <br/> <br/> my question is what is my n″žno are permanent address registration? I'm Ponaem and I'm wondering if, will become of the rent contract or something?</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q831179_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U10676" RELC_USERNAME="U10676">
<RelCText>You need permission from the owners, if you did get it. Some do not give to not become abuse.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q831179_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U38631" RELC_USERNAME="U38631">
<RelCText>Title deed of the apartment and one owner to give consent and your personal cards eace:p:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q831179_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U505565" RELC_USERNAME="U505565">
<RelCText>Thanks for the reply:)</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q831179_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U283021" RELC_USERNAME="U283021">
<RelCText>The owner, personally, a copy of which remains in the municipality and you LK. <br/> There fill out declarations by all.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q831179_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U276123" RELC_USERNAME="U276123">
<RelCText>Usually landlords allow current address. Otherwise – goes in the municipality of s″bstvenika and the deed to the property, pay some fees and to fill in the blanks. If it is permanent, then walk up to it and the INTERIOR MINISTRY to change the IDs.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q832911">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Health problems" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q832911" RELQ_USERID="U506388" RELQ_USERNAME="U506388">
<RelQSubject>Question about TEMP </RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi, I don't know if the topic is in the right place, but if not please excuse! <br/> I have the following questions, I have hypertension (blood pressure of 90 to 190/290/140, stroke without immobilization drawn surgery to remove pancreatic cyst to remove the spleen and tail of pancreas, gall stones, a defunct " " kidney and other stones , poor eyesight as a result of hypertension. If you think these complaints " " I'm certifying and taking a pension because you guessed it I netrudosposobna ... In addition, my surgery was 3 years ago and since then I have not paid contributions (it's understandable why) If this is a problem? Payroll taxes are to 450-500 BGN, but not how to pay for them, whether they will cut me out because of this? Thanks in advance and sorry again if I'm in the wrong section. </RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q832911_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U380745" RELC_USERNAME="U380745">
<RelCText>Yes, you can pass the TEMP with these diseases, but without insurance and recent studies and medical history reports, will hardly happen. <br/> can ask and the TEMP. At least there you take a user fee.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q832911_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U207104" RELC_USERNAME="U207104">
<RelCText>There's a theme for TEMP, it was best to ask, but nothing. When you go for the first time must present: <br/> 2. The medical history of a hospital with the actual data for the diagnosis of the disease. That without health insurance is not going to happen, because you can't get to a hospital, you have to pay for my entire stay there and all studies. <br/> 2. You have to prepare documents for the initial appearance, and this is done by treating physician to take records and other paperwork you need. <br/> 3. If you come for the first time after it is ready, wait for at least 2-3 years until summoned. <br/> 4. as far as I understand in the past 3 years you've never been to control reviews and you have documents that you require in the TEMP, to certify that your condition has not improved and you need help. Where do we get them to old date? Anything that doesn't prove they reject him. <br/> starters pay payroll taxes, otherwise you can not do anything again, after a few years you'll have a chance. <br/> I am in sickness pension of 7 years, but I never stopped going to checkups every few months. I'm going with all the documents of the LEMC. <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q832911_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U465762" RELC_USERNAME="U465762">
<RelCText>Hi. I received a letter for an appearance before the Temp (this is not my first time) and they want me to submit CT of spine (so far never seeking), at the same time, they want a picture of vrat″. Just to make it clear that the trauma of my vrat″, broken cervical vertebrae after a crash. My question is there any way to drop Kat because it is very vredena the whole procedure. I don't want to bombard me so much radiation, and the other what I don't understand is why if there is a cat and want a photo. more exposure:(</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q832911_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U507007" RELC_USERNAME="U507007">
<RelCText>For re-certification took up the disability of the child% from 30% to 50% the Commission is delayed 9 months with setting the date for appearance for those months ago is a monthly supplement and double children retroactively.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q832911_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U207104" RELC_USERNAME="U207104">
<RelCText>[quote author = Hrisi 80 link = topic = 832911. msg30417849 # msg30417849 date = 1426840810] <br/> In re-certification took up the disability of the child% from 30% to 50% the Commission is delayed 9 months with setting the date for appearance for those months ago is a monthly supplement and double children retroactively. <br/> [/quote] <br/>, To apply for social services. You take at once.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q833599">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Housing and property" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q833599" RELQ_USERID="U477739" RELQ_USERNAME="U477739">
<RelQSubject>Questions about renting an apartment</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi <br/> change ahead of us a home and I have a few doubts about whether there is a change in hiring procedures. When I rented this apartment, it all happened very quickly and seamlessly-meeting was with the landlord and real estate office and almost immediately signed the Treaty in their presence. The landlord showed me a document for ownership, identity card, deposit and gave him a bike and he gave me the keys. <br/> currently the case is that you have to give a deposit, and then the broker wants to sign a contract and pay a deposit to the landlord, and only upon receipt of the keys to pay the first installment for the rent. This is the practice in most cases? I'm a little uncertain, so I'm interested in, as well as what must I require of the broker in this case: mediation contract, a deed for the property, personal documents, receipt for deposit and/or deposit? </RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q833599_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U474449" RELC_USERNAME="U474449">
<RelCText>Make sure the broker is from a legitimate firm. I mean, it's not a " Amateur ". All listed documents: <br/> mediation contract, a deed for the property, personal documents, receipt for deposit and/or deposit? I think that will be of benefit.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q833599_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U492341" RELC_USERNAME="U492341">
<RelCText>And to me so they wanted, but we refused because it seemed doubtful and so accidentally found a new one from a private individual. We loved paid a rent and a deposit, we did the contract and gave us the keys immediately. Be careful with these brokers.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q833599_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U371751" RELC_USERNAME="U371751">
<RelCText>Don't let cash advance! <br/> Number of type of " deposit to take off from the site " are infinite offensive. Otherwise, the practice is a rental deposit + payment of the first car, but upon signing of the contract. Komisinnata for the broker after signature of the contract, but still depends on your arrangement. Standard is 1/2 of the agreed rent. <br/> <br/> Practice is broker to first say how others are no good and that it is your broker that you will find what you're looking for the perfect price-performance ratio. <br/> <br/> Read carefully what you sign!!!!!! As to convince that this is the standratna form. read</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q833599_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U477739" RELC_USERNAME="U477739">
<RelCText>Thanks for the guidance! <br/> Broker wants a down payment, it offered to other customers. Though slightly as extortion, I don't see how could I tell him no. Other brokers said the same thing about my deposit, so I think it would normal practice. <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q833599_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U492341" RELC_USERNAME="U492341">
<RelCText>Well, they are quick and eager not to change your mind, don't quit, and they money to izkaratMnogo nerve.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q834523">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Klûkarnik" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q834523" RELQ_USERID="U2227" RELQ_USERNAME="U2227">
<RelQSubject>Question to cheat, who work at a bank</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Many wondered where to make my request and finally I decided to put it here.   Please moderators excused if I have the wrong place. <br/> <br/> in search of I company offering sewing of corporate clothing (shirt, jacket, pants, skirt) for Office employees (male and female) on the Internet   I searched a lot, but I did come up with companies specialized in this area they gave me a very high asking prices. I'm looking for a good combination of quality and price as the price for a suit (jacket-skirt/jacket-pants) does not exceed 80-85   euro, and the shirt-16-17 euro. My budget is such that we have to meet those prices, mean and total quantity to be ordered, and it is not a little. <br/> I remembered that most banks carry corporate clothing and in this connection, if there is someone who works in a bank or a company knows that sew garments like to recommend it to me. Maybe personal, for not to do advertising. <br/> thanks in advance to all who respond to my question.:  : bouquet <br/> Remains in the hope someone answer me, because for me finding the right company is Tuesday ...:  : tired <br/></RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834523_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U448084" RELC_USERNAME="U448084">
<RelCText>These banks are not known as the most economical user ... Why don't you find a company that sew school uniforms, there is emphasis on bûdžetnostta  : thinking:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834523_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U2227" RELC_USERNAME="U2227">
<RelCText>I asked one such company, but from there told me that the work on other standards (children's), used different materials than those that are required for this type of clothing and do not want to take on such a responsibility. <br/> Directed me to look elsewhere.  : whistle:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834523_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U82089" RELC_USERNAME="U82089">
<RelCText>Sew them as ugly uniforms, that last one is my shirt sleeve on the shortcut from the other with cm, not to mention how ugly the cut. Find a company that has nice clothes, ready to ask, as a quantity discount. But again I don't believe fit in that amount.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834523_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U142629" RELC_USERNAME="U142629">
<RelCText>[quote author = adelinda link = topic = 834523. msg30432171 # msg30432171 date = 1427007389] <br/> sew them as ugly uniforms, that last one is my shirt sleeve on the shortcut from the other with cm, not to mention how ugly the cut. Find a company that has nice clothes, ready to ask, as a quantity discount <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> Absolutely. They're so ugly Bank uniforms, not to mention the quality of the fabrics. Years ago when I worked at UBB Women sewed them Dams, now suppose that another company. Not to mention that, in four years they couldn't hit my number  : ooooh: and I think you need to find a company with better clothes.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834523_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U25755" RELC_USERNAME="U25755">
<RelCText>I've been working uniform many years ago. And then wasn't cheap. <br/> advise to escape from Sakata. Are inapplicable to work year-round. Difficult to maintain, require at least once a month cleaning. Why would you do this cost of your employees? <br/> shirt (summer/winter) with a spectacular scarf/tie is very appropriate solution for low budget <br/> proceed to local firms, which would give volume discount. <br/> For the region of Varna-troshevo and Theodora. Their factories are near the city, there are speed dating, comment on fabrics in samples, discounts for quantity. <br/> success!</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q834578">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Klûkarnik" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q834578" RELQ_USERID="U507424" RELQ_USERNAME="U507424">
<RelQSubject>Question on ID card</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>[b] Hi I have a big problem and I would be happy if someone help me or answer the question. Six months ago I came to Germany to learn the language and to work with my parents, however on March 6 was my birthday and then I turned 18 years old and the bad news is that that's when my identity card. It is now expired shelf life of 16 days and after 1 week I want to travel to Bulgaria. Here in Berlin there is a Bulgarian Embassy and we went there two months ago to tell them that my personal card expires and if possible from here to make the ID card they said it was possible that they photographed me, I signed up we paid 30 euros and they told me that to 2 months they're going to call me to come pick up the card. However, there is no call yet but after 1 week I have to travel and my question is whether it will let me get to the crates and Bulgaria with an expired ID card. just at the moment I'm super nervous, because those at the Embassy if you don't call me soon I force you will stay here in Germany by having   call me ... Please help ... [/b]</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834578_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U91384" RELC_USERNAME="U91384">
<RelCText>What do we call the Embassy and ask them when and how to travel. I don't think I could with an expired card.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834578_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U507424" RELC_USERNAME="U507424">
<RelCText>I am writing here, because someone else had the same problem and answer me so ...</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834578_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U45754" RELC_USERNAME="U45754">
<RelCText>What confused them with your customs what documents will you travel? <br/> If so hyper to travel (and from your post it seems to be rather " want "!) by the Embassy will issue laissez-passer. In Bulgaria will make your Passport, you will come back with him in Germany and you will get your personal map. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834578_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U484347" RELC_USERNAME="U484347">
<RelCText>The Embassy told you what and how. Seek them for development, not in the Forum. If they tell you that the card is not ready, then turn to the Forum.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834578_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U507424" RELC_USERNAME="U507424">
<RelCText>This pasavant cost to 70 euros in a pinch will get to this option just isn't that famous Forum ush can't all live in Bulgaria, and no one had a similar problem and that   write here and the Embassy is closed today</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q834586">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Klûkarnik" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q834586" RELQ_USERID="U154375" RELQ_USERNAME="U154375">
<RelQSubject>legal question</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Sell an apartment, which has many descendants. In this case, I was willing to sell, but not at such a low price. Only that I have only 1/3 of a room. Threaten to sue me and put it up for auction. According to some lawyers, it is entirely possible, according to the other there is no way without my signature. To file suit even how long it will take?</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834586_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U242733" RELC_USERNAME="U242733">
<RelCText>honestly, if you've got 1/3 of the room it's pointless to do a problem. Like sell it take part and let it go. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834586_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U154375" RELC_USERNAME="U154375">
<RelCText>To stay on the street. That's why I'm asking</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834586_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U316897" RELC_USERNAME="U316897">
<RelCText>And double the price to sell, the money from the 1/3 room you go to collect your new roof  : roll:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834586_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U154375" RELC_USERNAME="U154375">
<RelCText>So we have a little bit of land separately. But for those funny money better to go to the auction and they do not take anything, once you are so desperate to stay on the street. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q834586_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U10569" RELC_USERNAME="U10569">
<RelCText>Buy back their parts and then you won't be in the street.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q835098">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Klûkarnik" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q835098" RELQ_USERID="U457808" RELQ_USERNAME="U457808">
<RelQSubject>Current address-Question?</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>I have no idea where my question, sorry if I don't belong here, but I couldn't find a more appropriate. My question is this: my permanent address is in Plovdiv and for now I have no intention to change it. However, I am currently a student in Sofia and I want to change my present address. I know what documents you need, but as I read through the Internet anywhere wrote that once changed it have 30 days to state that where I have to say, they don't fit somewhere in the system directly address?, and also it is not necessary to change the identity card and other documents right?</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q835098_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U503253" RELC_USERNAME="U503253">
<RelCText>Identity card no need to change it. You must register the new circumstances, if you have registered in the Labour Office Directorate " ". (if you want, of course).</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q835098_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U457808" RELC_USERNAME="U457808">
<RelCText>[quote author = snowgirl link = topic = 835098. msg30459911 # msg30459911 date = 1427288026] <br/> ID no need to change it. You must register the new circumstances, if you have registered in the Labour Office Directorate " ". (if you want, of course). <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> No, actually, that's the main reason I want to change my current address so I can write in the employment office in Sofia and this many wondering where I have to say this change, thanks for the reply.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q835098_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U13699" RELC_USERNAME="U13699">
<RelCText>In The Municipality. And you must be the owner of the property with deed, as it fills in a declaration that agrees to be his address.  :p: eace</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q835098_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U409491" RELC_USERNAME="U409491">
<RelCText>[quote author = seangelova link = topic = 835098. msg30460087 # msg30460087 date = 1427289131] <br/> [quote author = snowgirl link = topic = 835098. msg30459911 # msg30459911 date = 1427288026] <br/> ID no need to change it. You must register the new circumstances, if you have registered in the Labour Office Directorate " ". (if you want, of course). <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> No, actually, that's the main reason I want to change my current address so I can write in the employment office in Sofia and this many wondering where I have to say this change, thanks for the reply ... <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> If you're a student and you live in studentski grad dorm room upon check-in, would you request the certificate for the current address. If it is the case, ask the host of the dorm, to orient you to the municipality of Student, if you don't know alone. You go to the Town Hall in studentski grad, or where you live, there will direct you and pass application. I know that one of the necessary documents for approved for residence is an order for accommodation in residence, plus ID card, to be filled in an application, paid and issued the certificate. If you don't have such an order, you probably need to submit a certificate, you're a full-time student, and if you don't live in a rental agreement or other similar document for the municipality in which you live.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q835098_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U457808" RELC_USERNAME="U457808">
<RelCText>The owner's not coming with me, everything is very well researched, the owner will make the notarized statement and it will go to the municipality where you need to fill out and application. <br/> No, I live in a student city and I am not for hire. Live in the apartment of my relatives ... my idea was if someone recently changed current address to tell whether I have to go somewhere and say change. At the moment and my current and permanent address are my newsm78 in Plovdiv. Thanks for the answers though:)</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q837074">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Credit and leasing" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q837074" RELQ_USERID="U508707" RELQ_USERNAME="U508707">
<RelQSubject>question about loans?</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>A friendly family (they were married ten years ago) tegliha many loans – 1-2 family (over 15 000 BGN, as far as I know) to several of the big banks in Bulgaria + many of these quick loans who have immense interest (if ever asked me, I would tell them not to engage in such nonsense ...). I don't know exactly what they were doing them all the money, however I know some business with the store evolved and eventually closed, all lived in the House, you're not paid contributions anywhere and so much time until 5-6 months, when you went in Europe (somewhere in the Czech Republic) would work, and maybe to hide I don't know. And so to the other day, when I contacted me and sent me a 300-euro to deposit in one of all their loans, as they gave me their data. I am of course fully aware that those $ 300 there is nothing to do, but theirs is the solution, so I went and I put them. However, the woman there told me that the situation is very serious, and if you don't have Court are my relatives, for example, to run away from them. Now I don't know what to tell them, but my question is, what can happen to them, if you come to Bulgaria? I mean, the part with the bailiff are past it, because they don't have anything their already here, but is there any danger of imprisonment or something? If someone has an idea how it works, because I in my life I've never had such a problem, and they are so mired in trouble and that if I wanted to no how to help them financially, for example, if nothing else at least some advice to give? :) <br/></RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q837074_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U318157" RELC_USERNAME="U318157">
<RelCText>There's nothing to do, nor what to take. Naturally piling up their interest and finally all these obligations will remain for their heirs. Although in unasledvane of obligations still have loopholes. <br/> That running away from them, I don't understand why you said that. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q837074_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U508707" RELC_USERNAME="U508707">
<RelCText>[quote author = tkirilova link = topic = 837074. msg30531899 # msg30531899 date = 1428065215] <br/> has nothing to make them, nor what to take. Naturally piling up their interest and finally all these obligations will remain for their heirs. Although in unasledvane of obligations still have loopholes. <br/> That running away from them, I don't understand why you said that. <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> I've heard of these loopholes, that becomes a sort of legacy opt-out, if I'm not mistaken, because a friend of mine had a problem with his father, but after he died, the familiar dropped the legacy, and I don't know what exactly is happening in such a case, the obligations, but he currently does not owe a penny of State. <br/> <br/> regarding bank employee and I do not know much He wants to tell me when I'm gone and just ask for the information, nor do I want something specific by it or anything.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q837074_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U318157" RELC_USERNAME="U318157">
<RelCText>Just so happens to like give up succession. <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q837074_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U283021" RELC_USERNAME="U283021">
<RelCText>Yes, but if you give up heritage, give up everything, not just from the credits.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q837074_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U508707" RELC_USERNAME="U508707">
<RelCText>[quote author = tkirilova link = topic = 837074. msg30531944 # msg30531944 date = 1428065505] <br/> Just happens to like give up succession. <br/> <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> well and in such a case, what happens to the obligations that it became interesting? Banks, fast loans and everyone else wouldn't in any way looking for money?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q838012">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Our home" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q838012" RELQ_USERID="U477800" RELQ_USERNAME="U477800">
<RelQSubject>Solar hot water system-questions:)</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi <br/> Pretty dug around the Forum and read all that he had on the issue, but in my case more confused than before I started ...  : lol:: lol:: lol: <br/> So the case is as follows: <br/> House on 3 floors with dvuskatov roof <br/> 80 l Boiler. with 2 coils on the first floor, one is hooked up to a local heating, the other is a free <br/> 80 l Boiler. on the third floor without streamers, too likely to change very soon and get the heater with 2 heat exchangers. <br/> <br/> Questions are the following:   <br/> 1. What system to choose – Open (without pressure) or closed (with pressure, I don't want to have the pressure vessel cover)? The distance from the floor to the water heater tank 3 (mountainside) will be somewhere around 2 feet. <br/> 2. To be tied to the system water heaters or be tied to Plumbing installation? <br/> 3. What size pipes should be placed for the connection of the system with water boilers? As far as I read the best option are copper, but how big? 16 mm, 18 mm? <br/> 4. What is the best solar system in terms of price/performance according to you, which we can buy and which company would you recommend from experience for Sofia? <br/> 5. Vakumnotr″ben manifold or selective collector? May the first? <br/> <br/> If there are additional questions that I have not mentioned will be happy to answer.  :D <br/> many thanks in advance for sharing experience and opinions.  : bouquet:  ::  : bouquet bouquet:</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838012_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U477800" RELC_USERNAME="U477800">
<RelCText>Nobody's been down that road?  : cry:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838012_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U398821" RELC_USERNAME="U398821">
<RelCText>Hi, we have built a solar system of the Villa. It is best to visit 2-3 companies offering the service and take your questions to them. I can't be helpful because with this part gone I. And on the Internet you can find a lot of information. <br/> here, I found this:p:   quick eace <br/> http://www.emde-solar.com/%D1%82%D0%B5%D1%85%D0%BD%D0%BE%D0%BB%D0%BE%D0%B3%D0%B8%D0%B8 <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838012_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U220394" RELC_USERNAME="U220394">
<RelCText>[quote author = petkova8887 link = topic = 838012. msg30566571 # msg30566571 date = 1428491022] <br/> nobody's been down that road?  : cry: <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> petkova, two boilers with a little   don't know how I will do it. Two rounds will you need two pumps, two controls? Either one, but the hot fluid as I go through one water heater goes on the other. Or via three-way valve in temperature to be allocated where needs warming ...   Or only 80 l. to light up with solar is a waste, to me, is the water heater 300 l is situated on the ground floor, and the roof are solarite tube time is 15 yards and again after the summer, in-3 hours sunshine if no water is starting to overheat, enough whining-140 degrees .... <br/> System under pressure. I don't know without pressure accordingly without pump that efektivvna, the gražitačen principle. In so doing, whether at all is possible for Solari, this is not a boiler to heat the water, getting warmed up. Here the panels are shining and they are on the roof, how will you get in hot water in the coil? <br/> system doesn't make any sense to SHOUT, it's used to propylene glycol does not freeze in the winter. Inačče can only be dopl″lva, but through the valve, not from the tap so that the circle is a coil-pump-collector. To be safe (right passes through the boiler by means of the coil), propylene is used rather than ethylene glycol (antifreeze) which is poisoned. <br/> to me are French and the boiler and door panels, Šafoto, the management is German. The pipes are made of copper, 15 or 18, may 18, and insulation is from true black and maximum fat-28 in remembrance. <br/> Collectors are flat, not from the pipe, of time (4 years ago) were the last scream, cost around $ 3000, two whole installation without the pipes (we bet them in advance) went out about 6. <br/> For summer work system for winter helps to heat the boiler not by 5 and 15-25 degrees ... <br/> My Megaterm do have a website. Some are wooden philosophers, but they work, they did things in nâkoplko dol″lnitelno guarantee are not garbage men belong ... <br/> But best consult several companies and see what you offer. <br/> Ceb again, miracles do not wait. Just make an account how much will also use the system and how long will it take to redeem your investment ... Will see if it's worth it, the individual is, of course. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838012_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U477800" RELC_USERNAME="U477800">
<RelCText>Feria, thanks, I've read that  ;-) <br/> <br/> StefanB, thank you very much for the detailed response. <br/> On profitability, both the water heater are my 3 sq <br/> Upper works 1-1.5 hours per day, i.e. 4 SQUARE, lower working on 2-2,5 hours a day, i.e. 7 kV. We have 4 + 7 = 11 M 2 SQUARE let them put a daily/nightly 50:50. daily and night 5.5 5.5 per day, per month are 165 165 daily and night for 7 months-April through October on. are 1155 SQUARE day and night. <br/> 1155 x 0.161052 = 186 euro daily <br/> 1155 = 0.072 x 83 euro night <br/> Euro 269 per year, if the power does not become more expensive. <br/> i.e. If I invest 1500 euro in system + installation + pipes need five years to her out. <br/> did I?  :D <br/> <br/> will rejoice and others to get involved with.  ) <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838012_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U220394" RELC_USERNAME="U220394">
<RelCText>[quote author = petkova8887 link = topic = 838012. msg30568651 # msg30568651 date = 1428505139] <br/> Feria, thanks, I've read that  ;-) <br/> <br/> StefanB, thank you very much for the detailed response. <br/> On profitability, both the water heater are my 3 sq <br/> Upper works 1-1.5 hours per day, i.e. 4 SQUARE, lower working on 2-2,5 hours a day, i.e. 7 kV. We have 4 + 7 = 11 M 2 SQUARE let them put a daily/nightly 50:50. daily and night 5.5 5.5 per day, per month are 165 165 daily and night for 7 months-April through October on. are 1155 SQUARE day and night. <br/> 1155 x 0.161052 = 186 euro daily <br/> 1155 = 0.072 x 83 euro night <br/> Euro 269 per year, if the power does not become more expensive. <br/> i.e. If I invest 1500 euro in system + installation + pipes need five years to her out. <br/> did I?  :D <br/> <br/> will rejoice and others to get involved with.  ) <br/> <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> As account-you know I guess not, according to the initial data, however: <br/> 1. A budget of $ 1500 for these money can take a solar with a upravleniel, as far as I've seen some announcements and handouts. For one boiler, if you just connect the coil and piping. (A) working conditions, pipes, installation ... A second water heater and any electronics that manage one to one or the other is shining ... <br/> <br/> 2. For such current consumption, I personally would not do. I hate when fitting you will break their tiles for $ 100, don't bother ... <br/> <br/> 3. If you want to make it sound, consider a big boiler, or buffer 1-1.5 tonnes to the boiler to the summer and greete Solari and where to get your HOT WATER and with these $ 1500 will bind it and adjust with electronics to the pot, then you're powering the entire House and is effectively. <br/> this from me, good luck! <br/> 2. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q838161">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Health problems" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q838161" RELQ_USERID="U65696" RELQ_USERNAME="U65696">
<RelQSubject>About Mole</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Surgeon or dermatologist for advice is sought and remove a mole? <br/> went to a surgeon, review it for 5 seconds with any lupička, concluded that there is nothing scary <br/> but due to the place where it is located, it is recommended that you remove <br/></RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838161_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U279639" RELC_USERNAME="U279639">
<RelCText>[quote author = Start link = topic = 838161. msg30566987 # msg30566987 date = 1428493622] <br/> a surgeon or dermatologist for advice is sought and remove a mole? <br/> went to a surgeon, review it for 5 seconds with any lupička, concluded that there is nothing scary <br/> but due to the place where it is located, it is recommended that you remove <br/> <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> of course leather doctor-I am premahvala in skin clinic in Plovdiv by dermatologist :peace:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838161_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U83747" RELC_USERNAME="U83747">
<RelCText>I've heard that sometimes you have to and consultation with the surgeon, because you have to consider dangerous is her Mole. There are cases of people who have lost because of a removed Mole.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838161_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U65696" RELC_USERNAME="U65696">
<RelCText>Me, I went to a surgeon-oncologist. He considered that the Mole is not dangerous, but rubbed continuously from underwear and better dismantle. When I asked him a dermatologist or a surgeon to perform the operation, said the surgeon. the personal hell of course insisted it be done in leather dispensary.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838161_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U12012" RELC_USERNAME="U12012">
<RelCText>Having already passed once through the removal of the mole, which was in its infancy as amended by the presence of malignant cells suggest; <br/> 1. Dermatologist or onco-dermatologist to see Mole <br/> 2. surgery is performed by a surgeon or neurosurgeon, depends on where it is located. Can possibly if not a bad place to off and onco-dermatologist.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838161_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U382932" RELC_USERNAME="U382932">
<RelCText>surgical oncologist. My dermatologist sent me to review surgical oncologist </RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q838983">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="I want a baby" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q838983" RELQ_USERID="U509448" RELQ_USERNAME="U509448">
<RelQSubject>Question about test ... I'm confused ....</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hello and happy holidays ... I want a baby of four months but not   gets today took an easy test, 4 minute nâk″dese ppoâvibleda pale pink feature that disappeared in 15 minutes. in the dark I'm 15 I need dojdea I nnikakvi symptoms other than chest pain, itch me, I don't know what to think anymore ...     :(</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838983_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U233670" RELC_USERNAME="U233670">
<RelCText>Chest pain and can just CMD is on off feature, never happened to me. I know that may appear with a delay and not a correct answer, but to appear and disappear newsm78: crazyeyes: don't think about it and wait for the day. There's no sense of that tension, I say this from experience. Nobody wants tears, if nothing had happened. Better pleasantly surprised than painfully disappointed. I wish you  : EFP: Write what happened, as soon as you know the final answer! :hug:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838983_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U509448" RELC_USERNAME="U509448">
<RelCText>Thanks I don't understand it. 15trâbva (e) and I came and I'm 22, if not come eestestveno. Will repeat the test in the morning:)</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838983_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U24648" RELC_USERNAME="U24648">
<RelCText>Testovete into account the true [u] after [/u] as there is a delay in the cycle. In my opinion, it makes no sense to take at this stage.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838983_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U55282" RELC_USERNAME="U55282">
<RelCText>And with both pregnancies I had before my test is delayed. First pregnancy line was so pale that he was on the verge of auto-suggestion. But still it didn't disappear. With the second pregnancy line became dark and clear very quickly, and I had more days to the expected cycle.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q838983_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U460161" RELC_USERNAME="U460161">
<RelCText>Every pregnancy test has a manual. I don't know what brand you use, but of these, of which I trust you, clearly wrote that the result is read after 5 minutes, no later than 10 minutes. Then the result is incorrect. Why you had to watch 15 minutes. in the test? : thinking: <br/> to its secure test after a delay. The test takes into account the levels of HCG. This hormone should be increased in order to reflect the test. Wait your being late. Success  :p eace:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q839073">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Health problems" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q839073" RELQ_USERID="U509468" RELQ_USERNAME="U509468">
<RelQSubject>AIDS-question</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi all, few days ago I had contact with a girl, razkasa detstvenata and the zipper and began to run a certain amount of blood I had a little blood in the abdomen and in one hand and I'm not looking if I did any of these sores over nails that are obtained as a result of nail biting nails, so my question is can I get infected with AIDS in some way I know that is absurd since this is the first sexual intercourse for her, but it can be transmitted from mother and that's why I'm worried. Sorry for the stupid question, but it always overwhelms me paranoia, I would like to ask you for only serious answers, I would also like to ask you can through the spit in the eye or on the skin. I apologize for stupid question but I want you to calm down. :?</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q839073_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U472340" RELC_USERNAME="U472340">
<RelCText>I don't know if I should cry or laugh!</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q839073_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U508287" RELC_USERNAME="U508287">
<RelCText>Do you think that her mother is sick from AIDS and her father?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q839073_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U242733" RELC_USERNAME="U242733">
<RelCText>If so afraid of explore, now and after six months, free of charge and anonymously. In theory, it is possible to everyone's sick of it all. Often speaking of the writing you is pure paranoia, but we're not going to relax until check out.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q839073_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U314508" RELC_USERNAME="U314508">
<RelCText>It is to laugh  : mrgreen:: mrgreen:: mrgreen:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q839073_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U47989" RELC_USERNAME="U47989">
<RelCText>[quote author = liola link = topic = 839073. msg30592119 # msg30592119 date = 1428901793] <br/> think her mom is sick from AIDS and her father? <br/> [/quote] <br/> is, it can be contaminated not only by parents, rather than needles, manipulaii. <br/> <br/> see nothing funny in that paranoia of the young man. It's better than unprotected sex. <br/> I wonder how old women to mock such a thing, if the topic is not skating. Here are found much more inadequate health issues of the elderly.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q839846">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Our home" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q839846" RELQ_USERID="U7954" RELQ_USERNAME="U7954">
<RelQSubject>About El. Kettle</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Because you're looking for. Kana with smaller capacity and no plastics in contact with the water looked more like ceramic. <br/> someone with an opinion about them? To have one at home? Are you satisfied? More small scale are, how long they heat up water? <br/> v″lnuvag me most of paddings of inviting <br/> https://zora.bg/gorenje/k-10-karim/22421 <br/> http://technika.bg/product/9036/elektricheska-kana-gorenje-k-10-c.html <br/> I suck attuned to the mark, but then fell in love with the invites to the picture at least, and seemed to have the most powerful than ceramic. <br/> options thinking glass pitcher, but again the lids and the filters are plastic. as with steel as a whole. And indeed most are huge, and we more than 2 cups of tea at a time, almost never make. <br/> <br/> So I collect all kinds of views and ideas on the subject:   bouquet:</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q839846_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U497738" RELC_USERNAME="U497738">
<RelCText>These invites are really very nice and 100% are better than plastic, but it seems to me that the more easily can break. I use a regular and I'm glad http://onebgshop.com/%D0%95%D0%BB%D0%B5%D0%BA%D1%82%D1%80%D0%B8%D1%87%D0%B5%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%B0-% D0% BA% D0% B0% D0% BD% D0% B0-% D0% B7% D0% B0-% D0% B1% D1% 8A% D1% 80% D0% B7% D0% BE-% D0% B7% D0% B0% D1% 82% D0% BE% D0% BF% D0% BB% D1% 8F% D0% BD% D0% B5% D0% BD-% D0% B0-% D0% B2% D0% BE% D0% B4% D0% B0-Benzer-BR-3201-KW</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q839846_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U30405" RELC_USERNAME="U30405">
<RelCText>Wow, they're beautiful! I have from Russia for the BREW kettles porcelain tea, but it is at times more convenient, because Sam &#242; you boil the water. The first time I've seen such. <br/> wonder whether with outdoor or indoor heater. If you are with an indoor, I would've taken one such beauty.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q839846_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U7954" RELC_USERNAME="U7954">
<RelCText>http://www.cpz.ru/Gorenje_K10C_665646/here is a picture in there, that may open.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q839846_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U30405" RELC_USERNAME="U30405">
<RelCText>No, that's what I mean (as I turn this off st″rčaŝoto)-metal plate at the bottom. Some pitchers have at the bottom a helical coil as got, which accumulate as scum, go clean it. This st″rčaŝoto don't know what it is, but it would certainly be easier than clean coil. <br/> sparked a lot to get one of those. File am tea with water boiled in a metal pot, and I don't know if my imagination, but it seems like there was a metallic aftertaste, while China is absolutely neutral. Brilliant and extremely beautiful instrument. : love: <br/> <br/> here is one video that represents the product (in Russian). <br/> <br/> [video] https://www.youtube.com/watch? v = IE_B6vTjzmM [/video]</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q839846_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U7954" RELC_USERNAME="U7954">
<RelCText>I watched this show. Frankly this metallic aftertaste. It's unpleasant, all kinds of   quality bottles for water stainless steel is not what I'm Nam tried, but they always give me such a metallic aftertaste and Super bugs me. .. If and when you invite so I give up I thought about this a moment ... <br/> st″rčaŝoto that honestly I don't know what is. <br/> Otherwise there's that http://techmart.bg/products/product_details/30005 <br/> and more http://www.narmagbg.com/search_9m.php?query=%D0%9A%D0%B0%D0%BD%D0%B0+%D0%B5%D0%BB%D0%B5%D0%BA%D1%82%D1%80%D0%B8%D1%87%D0%B5%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%B0+%D0%BA%D0%B5%D1%80%D0%B0%D0%BC%D0%B8%D1%87%D0%BD%D0%B0&amp;back_page=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.narmagbg.com%2Fshow_book.php%3Fisbn%3DJR -5602% 26isbn_mode% 3D1 &amp; submit = Search <br/> and elite but they have them in 1000 watt ... <br/> So overall I'm worried about the low Watts on how long it will take to boil the water.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q840910">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Diets and weight loss procedures" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q840910" RELQ_USERID="U510266" RELQ_USERNAME="U510266">
<RelQSubject>Question about weight loss</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi ladies I have a belly and want to remove it, I heard that a very effective way and great results are postigalo if you tie a plastic bag on the abdomen and running. My question is the following, I have a tattoo in the area of the belly if you tie this plastic bag if something happens to my tattoo?</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q840910_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U465050" RELC_USERNAME="U465050">
<RelCText>Can you delete for example. :D</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q840910_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U191804" RELC_USERNAME="U191804">
<RelCText>Your question to tatuto or for tummy? <br/> first are you answered Yes: lol: <br/> regarding the effect of the plastic bag-deep doubt <br/>, you come up with something else-sports, for example, diet ...</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q840910_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U468454" RELC_USERNAME="U468454">
<RelCText>There are quite a few articles already that the plastic bag has zero effect. Only you get very sweaty belly, that's all.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q840910_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U233670" RELC_USERNAME="U233670">
<RelCText>No, girl, if you slipped and went down tatusčeto down ...: ooooh:: 35:: 35:: 35:::: hahaha hahaha hahaha::::: mrgreen: hahaha:: love:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q840910_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U355222" RELC_USERNAME="U355222">
<RelCText>At least 200 crunches a day for several months and the result is in the bag: eace:p  .</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q841695">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Living abroad" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q841695" RELQ_USERID="U510627" RELQ_USERNAME="U510627">
<RelQSubject>Question for those living in Spain</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hello to all. I apologize, I walked right into it, too, but I think that only here I can find the answers to the questions which I struggle. It's that we need to make a decision whether to move to Spain or not. At the moment we live in England and I find it very hard to decide. The main question that interests me is what life we can afford with 2500 euro salary (clean money). This is the money that offer my husband for a start. Cham and is added to the annual bonus plus a car and a telephone. I may I will be on maternity leave and possibly then will start working in the same company. <br/> comes to the region of Murcia. We've been there before and generally like it, but I can't get a sense whether the money that will pay us are good for Spanish standards.</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q841695_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U436280" RELC_USERNAME="U436280">
<RelCText>2500evro cleanly, even without counting the other pluses are above average. <br/> average salary there is 1200 euro -1400 brand. <br/> Such money they take quite a bit of people, doctors, teachers and other well paid. If you have a bike 500evro, real will have at least 2000 for everything else that I was not a little, since there will be no fuel, car, etc. costs. Now if it's worth it or not, you decide, depends on what you are looking for and why you want to Spain England. <br/> Murcia, on the other hand is cheap, so only the area even with his salary going to live, of course not opulently, but quite normal. If one day you work, you will be well above the average Spaniard,   as standard.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q841695_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U8585" RELC_USERNAME="U8585">
<RelCText>From my position is more than 2500 are a decent amount of support per month. With bonuses on top by a no-brainer!</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q841695_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U177785" RELC_USERNAME="U177785">
<RelCText>2 500 euro are money that you can afford to live decently and are good for the standard here. However, it depends on what kind of life you're used to and what are your earnings in England. You can look at what sites are the rents in Murcia (if you'll pay one) and to choose what you'll have after you cover your expenses. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q841695_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U510627" RELC_USERNAME="U510627">
<RelCText>Thank you all for the answers. I saw already houses for rent on the Internet and navigate to something between 600 and 800 euros. The matter is that here we can say that we have a good life. We have a House (we pay the mortgage), normal work and pay. The problem is that where my husband works there is no chance for development in the next 10 years, and the work that is offered in the same company, only in Spain of a better position, only with Spanish contract and pay in euro, respectively. On the one hand I don't want to risk it, and I was like well if this is a chance for a better life. In England as a whole is good, but we have almost no social life, the weather is terrible, but it's kind of quiet around here (at least in that part where we live). Spain attracts us with beautiful weather, the sea, and maybe a new challenge. If it was just the two of us, my husband and I wouldn't have to think so much. But with a baby on the way is more difficult. I can't decide where we will give him a better future.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q841695_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U177785" RELC_USERNAME="U177785">
<RelCText>Consider things and on education. If you're going to have a child, this issue should not be underestimated. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q842538">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Klûkarnik" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q842538" RELQ_USERID="U510485" RELQ_USERNAME="U510485">
<RelQSubject>Question for astronomers-lovers</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi, a few days in the West in the evening I notice a star, which unlike the other flashes in a variety of colors, red, white and blue. It is clear that because of atmosfirata all stars sparkle, but this changes the colors more than any other. The others usually blink in one color. Who is she? It is located about southwest of Venus (the balcony looking to the West). I think it's this, but on the Internet and have not found which star is located at this location: [url = https://www.youtube.com/watch? v = la_c2Eac-gL] https://www.youtube.com/watch? v = gL-la_c2Eac [/url]</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q842538_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U11333" RELC_USERNAME="U11333">
<RelCText>With Google Sky Map or with   Star Chart isn't that clear?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q842538_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U485951" RELC_USERNAME="U485951">
<RelCText>And we've seen it in Burgas. I don't know what is.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q842538_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U510485" RELC_USERNAME="U510485">
<RelCText>As I ask in foreign forums say getting the standard cliché, that prečupvala the light from the atmosphere. This is the case, but other stars with the same luminosity goru places like this on the horizon doesn't sparkle with such force and so definitely don't change their colors.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q842538_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U52301" RELC_USERNAME="U52301">
<RelCText>As far as I know, Jupiter is currently in such a position, it appears very bright.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q842538_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U510485" RELC_USERNAME="U510485">
<RelCText>I think it might be Mercury, because at this time they say it must be above the horizon in the West after sunset anywhere.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q843725">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Engagement and wedding" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q843725" RELQ_USERID="U457808" RELQ_USERNAME="U457808">
<RelQSubject>Question about the marriage, change of address and surname</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi, my life and health are to marry next week and I would like to ask a few things, because it turns out that generally in the BG mom can give you much more reliable information than in any institution in Bulgaria 1 want to ask will we have any problems in the future if my future husband stay in the documents of different IP addresses. For now I don't want to change my address because no one knows the where will we live 100% next year even for the moment I am domiciled in one city, it is at 2, and live in 3. The other problem I have is that you have to get Government and European grants, but their payment will be when I am with my new name and with your new ID card (and again with his old surname) My question is, if someone was in a similar situation could not get my money from the Bank, they said they could not answer from the University also did not tell me anything specific. I would be very grateful if someone could share some info.</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q843725_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U66637" RELC_USERNAME="U66637">
<RelCText>[quote author = seangelova link = topic = 843725. msg30741840 # msg30741840 date = 1430739811] <br/> Hi, my life and health are to marry next week and I would like to ask a few things, because it turns out that generally in the BG mom can give you much more reliable information than in any institution in Bulgaria 1 want to ask will we have any problems in the future If my future husband stay in the documents of different IP addresses. For now I don't want to change my address, because I don't know where will we live 100% next year even for the moment I am domiciled in one city, it is at 2, and live in 3. The other problem I have is that you have to get Government and European grants but their payment will be when I am with my new name and with your new ID card (and again with his old surname), my question is if someone was in a similar situation could not get my money from the Bank, they said they could not answer from the University also did not tell me anything specific. I would be very grateful if someone could share some information. <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> no problem to stay different [b] [/b] permanent addresses-verified private:p: eace <br/> desirable is to register the address of residence, but that no one was following him; <br/> <br/> can keep his surname or to add his to yours:)-in the first case, you won't need to make a new ID card-:) and it's verified personally; <br/> <br/> for euro do not know:p this scholarship   eace: read what they said relaxing her, or write and ask them  : hug: <br/> <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q843725_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U275437" RELC_USERNAME="U275437">
<RelCText>For the address I can't tell you. As for the name-on receipt of the funds may carry a copy of the Act of marriage, to certify that the holder is you, but with a new name. I think this advice. <br/> PS Very happy family life you crave!  :bouquet:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q843725_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U153122" RELC_USERNAME="U153122">
<RelCText>There is one document that pulls from the municipality, may was the name of a certificate of identity, or something like it, pull it, it says that Petka Dara Petka and Dan are one and the same person. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q843725_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U66637" RELC_USERNAME="U66637">
<RelCText>[quote author = link = topic = Chick 843725. msg30742127 # msg30742127 date = 1430741886] <br/> Has one document, draw from the municipality, may was the name of a certificate of identity, or something like it, pull it, it says that Petka Dara Petka and Dan are one and the same person. <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> correct me if I'm wrong:) <br/> Declaration of identity of our names-writing it myself, the responsibility is yours, art. 313 NC:) but it does not apply everywhere <br/> certificate for identity of names – from the municipality, there are fee; <br/> <br/> I guess I'll have and legalization for foreign countries. <br/> and again: it's important what they wrote from the Organization granting the scholarship</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q843725_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U153122" RELC_USERNAME="U153122">
<RelCText>I don't remember how it was, but the document was not completed by me but by the municipality with signature and stamp, if you translate and legalize see no problem, in fact I would have no problem to have a scholarship. It's not like the only people to get married and to change their last name.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q845933">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Business, work, professions" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q845933" RELQ_USERID="U296718" RELQ_USERNAME="U296718">
<RelQSubject>Question for compensation for contraction of a public servant </RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi! <br/> In shortening of the civil servant </RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q845933_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U441152" RELC_USERNAME="U441152">
<RelCText>[quote author = Iaki link = topic = 845933. msg30812833 # msg30812833 date = 1431602508] <br/> Hi! <br/> When cutting civil servant makes his severance payment for those, such as get, if you apply for an example? Again in this sense if it is to be shortened and they offer you a place elsewhere, if you accept it and then soon you decide to leave it or there is a time limit in which you have no right to leave? <br/> <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> Depends on which article of the law on civil servants they had to shorten the benefit which you don't get kategoričto if file check-out. You can leave at any time not to live in a robovladelčesko society. Read the law on civil service and then ask questions if something is not clear.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q845933_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U296718" RELC_USERNAME="U296718">
<RelCText><br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> Depends on which article of the law on civil servants they had to shorten the benefit which you don't get kategoričto if file check-out. You can leave at any time not to live in a robovladelčesko society. Read the law on civil service and then ask questions if something is not clear. <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> this response helped me a lot!!! I thought I read the law of civil servant .... <br/> <br/> Please write with normal tone, and if you can help me, I don't need an inflated, worthless writings!</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q845933_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U441152" RELC_USERNAME="U441152">
<RelCText>[quote author = Iaki link = topic = 845933. msg30812932 # msg30812932 date = 1431603323] <br/> <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> Depends on which article of the law on civil servants they had to shorten the benefit which you don't get kategoričto if file check-out. You can leave at any time not to live in a robovladelčesko society. Read the law on civil service and then ask questions if something is not clear. <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> this response helped me a lot!!! I thought I read the law of civil servant .... <br/> <br/> Please write with normal tone, and if you can help me, I don't need an inflated, worthless writings! <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> Answered you all hypothetical questions-if you cut me if I offer another job, I don't know what you think by writing useless.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q845933_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U304257" RELC_USERNAME="U304257">
<RelCText>If you filed for check-out you don't get no compensation, no matter how long you've been in the administration. If you be more specific in your question, we can be more specific in your answer:-)</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q845933_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U296718" RELC_USERNAME="U296718">
<RelCText>I'm not</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q846215">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Feeding with infant formula milk power" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q846215" RELQ_USERID="U386952" RELQ_USERNAME="U386952">
<RelQSubject>one or two questions, first for the giving of pumpkin puree with</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>And I take temeta to ask one or two questions, first giving the puree with pumpkin. I've given a potato and carrot and I replaced the full midday meal. For the next week I think to give mashed potato and pumpkin. Can I give a whole jar (if baby wants, of course) or the fact that introducing new vegetable should give a little? <br/> <br/> Now because of the little carrot started to poop a little more thickly than usual. It's not constipated because aka once per day without problems. You can expect the pumpkin to keep things as they are at the moment or it is suspected that there might be some change?</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846215_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U469298" RELC_USERNAME="U469298">
<RelCText>[quote author = Dimitria Ivanova link = topic = 846215. msg30822499 # msg30822499 date = 1431710025] <br/> and I take temeta to ask one or two questions, first giving the puree with pumpkin. I've given a potato and carrot and I replaced the full midday meal. For the next week I think to give mashed potato and pumpkin. Can I give a whole jar (if baby wants, of course) or the fact that introducing new vegetable should give a little? <br/> <br/> Now because of the little carrot started to poop a little more thickly than usual. It's not constipated because aka once per day without problems. You can expect the pumpkin to keep things as they are at the moment or it is suspected that there might be some change? <br/> [/quote] <br/> and we started with the carrot and potato, but started to poop more densely and stopped the carrot. But ever since I tried pumpkin-puree. So now I eat everything that there is at least a little pumpkin.  : lol: <br/> My advice to you is to start with a whole jar, I give up a half of small for a new product. If already on the next day, then there's nothing more ... Keep in mind that the potatoes with pumpkin is very densely/if you give purees of hip/, I mix the potato with pumpkin with pumpkin-less often, or with water, but won't be so sweet ... You can try and clean pumpkin-would love more  :p: eace;-) <br/> Pumpkin doesn't bake, adjust IE won't poop so densely as now.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846215_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U386952" RELC_USERNAME="U386952">
<RelCText>Thanks for the information. <br/> <br/> But didn't think to ask one more thing. After I've already replaced the midday meal may instead of dohranvam with milk to give first a little potato and carrot, and then potato and pumpkin? So again I'm not going to eat a whole jar of paste and you will know what is the reaction.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846215_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U469298" RELC_USERNAME="U469298">
<RelCText>[quote author = Dimitria Ivanova link = topic = 846215. msg30824506 # msg30824506 date = 1431749687] <br/> Thanks for the information. <br/> <br/> But didn't think to ask one more thing. After I've already replaced the midday meal may instead of dohranvam with milk to give first a little potato and carrot, and then potato and pumpkin? So again I'm not going to eat a whole jar of paste and will know what the reaction is. <br/> [/quote] <br/> To do so, mix 5-6 spoons of the new product with the old and I just mixed everything portion. <br/> don't be afraid to mix different purees-that's how you get better. :))))</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846215_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U386952" RELC_USERNAME="U386952">
<RelCText>Super! Thank you once again.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846215_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U318762" RELC_USERNAME="U318762">
<RelCText>Forgive my ignorance, but the pumpkin is a fruit or vegetable? The first pûrence that the child was from the only pumpkin Hip, unlike the only carrots that Hip slightly hives and ended it. You will not, however, my pediatrician's Office and said hey this is " fruit ", I wanted to start with the vegetables.  : mrgreen: <br/> <br/> and one more thing: don't you pûrencata you have to mix with milk to " fat-and-vegetable "? <br/> <br/> I dilute with milk and fruit.   newsm78</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q846450">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Elementary education" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q846450" RELQ_USERID="U51371" RELQ_USERNAME="U51371">
<RelQSubject>Question to the teacher or principal</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Girls, it happened to me the following: <br/> on April 27, my son got sick and went to my doctor on the 28th, which, respectively, they ate his treat. In the afternoon he went to school for 4 hours, because at that time to test that did not want to miss and bought candy to treat class as same day birthday. There's 4, 5 and 6 hour/ultimate/. <br/> Has a note from my doctor for the days which has not been to school <br/> his Class refused to excuse absences for 3/1,2 28 and 3 hour/as it was by the book. <br/> in the rules of the school, there is no such text, I sought and in other legal documents of the Inspectorate and the Ministry but nothing found. <br/> Please if there is anyone who is aware of to include <br/> thanks!</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846450_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U325053" RELC_USERNAME="U325053">
<RelCText>According to me it doesn't make sense not to excuse absences, the child has been to the doctor yet, there's a note. <br/> <br/> What you equal breath sounds for those absences, writing him 3 neizvineni. Your child will not become less good in the presence of student absences.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846450_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U474449" RELC_USERNAME="U474449">
<RelCText>And according to me makes no sense not to excuse his absence  . What is the opinion of the teacher, if the child becomes ill 4, 5, 6 hours and have to leave? </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846450_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U51371" RELC_USERNAME="U51371">
<RelCText>I jammed stuck, but events such as " to others but not to you " my. His class has some sort of personal attitude, so to speak, they have their history and these three absences are another story. I don't want to drive with a class or with a paralegal. Directors, just care reference is there an obstacle to be excused absences, these three just-right:)</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846450_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U18088" RELC_USERNAME="U18088">
<RelCText> If the child has a note, the class there is no reason to excuse his absence. The note is for the 28th, right?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846450_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U329941" RELC_USERNAME="U329941">
<RelCText>[quote author = NA MAMA ....? link = topic = 846450. msg30827187 # msg30827187 date = 1431785384] <br/> and according to me makes no sense not to excuse his absence  . What is the opinion of the teacher, if the child becomes ill 4, 5, 6 hours and have to leave? <br/> [/quote] that's exactly what happened with my son. Got headache, lassitude, vielo's world, and in addition he started raising the temperature. Give me a call the paramedic to take it home. Last 4, 5, 6 hour was gone. The other day I realized that his absences were written. But it is healthy to me, what to do.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q846505">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Of the market" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q846505" RELQ_USERID="U429044" RELQ_USERNAME="U429044">
<RelQSubject>Question about return </RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi! On 16 April predâvih in for Dainichi return furniture broken sofa. According to the Treaty had in the 30-day time limit is fixed and according to me. Today, I'm sure that on Monday will not call me to pick it up. I read that I have a right of cancellation of the contract and, accordingly, to save money however the couch is a few months old. How should I proceed from here any special documents you wear? Someone has dealt with this problem?</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846505_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U40709" RELC_USERNAME="U40709">
<RelCText>Look here-http://www.kzp.bg/index.php? mode = viewd &amp; group_id = 47 &amp; document_id = 4617 <br/> [quote] if the dealer does not make the product in accordance with the contract within a month, you have the right to claim for a refund of the amount you paid or discount of the price of the goods. <br/> should know, however, that you cannot claim for reimbursement of the amount paid If the non-compliance of the purchased goods is negligible. <br/> <br/> If you don't reach an agreement with the merchant, you can lodge a complaint against him to the nearest regional Office of the Commission for the protection of consumers or by email. [/quote]</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846505_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U429044" RELC_USERNAME="U429044">
<RelCText>Thank you for the information. I'm going to call on Monday to see what happens even though I am not hopeful of the friendly dealers.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846505_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U19330" RELC_USERNAME="U19330">
<RelCText>Interesting topic on every return. <br/> <br/> <br/> to prove what is negligible, which can be claimed, etc.. <br/> <br/> Dazi Commission I paid for them and they definitely don't do the work. <br/> <br/> <br/> What was the outcome of the situation. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846505_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U429044" RELC_USERNAME="U429044">
<RelCText>Hi! The couch was not repaired within the 30-day time limit, respectively, by law, had the right to cancellation of the contract and the recovery of the amount. I called and explained the situation they tried to lie, of course, with me even more angry. Eventually I asked for a cancellation of the contract and still seamlessly the same day gave me back my money, paid by me to the couch. Of course at first, Su tried to go by meter, but after performing their law and I stand up for my rights and I will t″rs′ the assistance of KZP immediately turned the pancake and n′mah problem</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q846505_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U19330" RELC_USERNAME="U19330">
<RelCText>Well, that they were understood, " " very glad of a good outcome. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q847115">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Klûkarnik" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q847115" RELQ_USERID="U395646" RELQ_USERNAME="U395646">
<RelQSubject>Question related to urban transport</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi! <br/> <br/> Use travel card on behalf of the disabled,   my name is printed on the plastic surgery as a chaperone/Map is the name of my husband's grandmother, she has Alzheimer's, we take care of it. Today refused to load the map, because it had "a new directive, according to which the cripple's come or do NTO. Certified power of attorney. Of course, this will become difficult. I read the Ordinance for SG, but such innovations not found. My question is, do they have the right to impose such a requirement, given that my names also appear on the map? <br/> My second question is what kind of documents do I need to change one of the attendants, whose names are printed on the map/there are currently my and my mother's name, but it will be a long time out of the country and take a wife that caters to the disabled person, we want to give, respectively, and to use the map/? Where should I submit these documents? From the Center for urban mobility transferred me to the Agency for social assistance, and the latter to the former. But, my idea is to be prepared to walk the woman not vain and downThe. administrations <br/> <br/> thanks in advance for any comments! <br/> <br/> <br/> Greetings! <br/></RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847115_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U25545" RELC_USERNAME="U25545">
<RelCText>Your case is not customary, and hardly anyone here   had a similar. Recommend to refer in writing to the Sofia Municipality, Centre for urban mobility in the virtual registry. You will receive a detailed written reply that the employees will have to comply, and will not be wondering if and why you back your back  :p: eace <br/> <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847115_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U481176" RELC_USERNAME="U481176">
<RelCText>The first question, Yes, it's new requirement, indicate the order of paper in offices, on my close even told her appointment. It's likely to be challenged that order, the website of CGM from 11.05.2015 is this message: <br/> <br/> " in connection with the numerous inquiries about the order and the manner of loading vehicles documents of persons with disabilities to inform that there is no change in the conditions under which transport documents are loaded from our stations. <br/> <br/> Loading may be going from the entitled person with an identity document or by his authorized representative with a certified power of Attorney power of Attorney, a copy of which he provided on every boot of the transport document. <br/> Reminder and the requirement of para. 2 of art. 29 of the Ordinance on the terms and conditions for travel with public transport in the territory of Sofia Municipality: <br/> (2) electronic Cards. issue/load the lists approved by the Social Welfare Department in " " Sofia Municipality and the identity card of the party so entitled (birth certificate-for children up to age 14) <br/> according to required an interpretative decision of the Commission for the protection of personal data loading an eligible card by another person becomes the only authorized person. " <br/> <br/> [url = http://www.sofiatraffic.bg/bg/news/1580/zarezhdane-na-karti-za-patuvane] http://www.sofiatraffic.bg/bg/news/1580/zarezhdane-na-karti-za-patuvane [/url] <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847115_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U395646" RELC_USERNAME="U395646">
<RelCText>BirdsFlu, you're absolutely right. The only thing that bothers me is that last time when I turned to writing Center for urban mobility was in 2013. and I'm still waiting for reply. <br/> not to mention that the phone also behave. <br/> poems, and thanks for your comment. <br/>  : bouquet:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847115_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U481176" RELC_USERNAME="U481176">
<RelCText>[quote author = Gina L. link = topic = 847115. msg30847741 # msg30847741 date = 1432037146] <br/>, the only thing that bothers me is that last time when I turned to writing Center for urban mobility was in 2013. and I'm still waiting for reply. <br/> <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/>   're not alone:) <br/> Put the request through the virtual registry of Sofia Municipality, from the drop-down menu choose Assistant. Mayor of transportation. <br/> [url = http://www.sofia.bg/virtdelovodstvo.asp] http://www.sofia.bg/virtdelovodstvo.asp [/url] <br/> sank my complaint when he was only, and nothing to CGM, but as I wrote in the Web site of co, had an answer. Another question was satisfactory. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847115_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U84943" RELC_USERNAME="U84943">
<RelCText>Even 15 years ago. I had a power of Attorney from my mom/cripple/and I was charging the card with him. Again returned the requirement. <br/> Each Notar. firm endorsed the site, into the home of the patient if it is fixed. You just have to ride to the notary's Assistant and then return it to the Office by car. If all is prepared in advance takes no more than 2 pm doesn't have to be a general authorisation-only referred to Socialist. care and SOFIA. <br/> For changing the name of the authorized and then wanted to go to the Socialist. care. But I don't know the details, I was the sole user of the card. <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q847117">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Deposits and savings" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q847117" RELQ_USERID="U14514" RELQ_USERNAME="U14514">
<RelQSubject>Supplementary pension scheme-about Allianz</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hello, <br/> have access to your personal insurance batch of soon, and I saw for years accumulated amount. My question is can I pull a part of available funds in it and what is the order? Who has experience in this, please share  . Thank    : bouquet:</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847117_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U283021" RELC_USERNAME="U283021">
<RelCText>For compulsory pension insurance? <br/> second pillar? <br/> If Yes, the answer is [b] not [/b].</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847117_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U494903" RELC_USERNAME="U494903">
<RelCText>What kind of pension insurance fund? If it is obligatory-you can't. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847117_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U14514" RELC_USERNAME="U14514">
<RelCText>Thanks to all <br/> <br/> I draw is when the retirement age only? <br/>  : bouquet:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847117_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U283021" RELC_USERNAME="U283021">
<RelCText>Withdrawal may not be possible. <br/> Only get your pension. <br/> If God forbid die, then the heirs receive the remainder in batch.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847117_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U529317" RELC_USERNAME="U529317">
<RelCText>Hi from me! And I have a question about Allianz. I have a voluntary pension fund to Allianz. My question is whether the Voluntary funds can withdraw the accumulated funds, as far as I know this kept not Mandatory. Thanks in advance!</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q847142">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Health problems" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q847142" RELQ_USERID="U44643" RELQ_USERNAME="U44643">
<RelQSubject>Chickenpox-a few questions?</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi, I have a few questions about chickenpox and will be happy to get an answer from the familiar: <br/> 1. Is it possible to infect a child by another child was in contact with contact? <br/> 2. Preboleduvali from chicken pox can be carriers of the virus after contact with sick? <br/> 3. What are the chances to infect a child in conversation in minutes with sick child outside without contact? <br/> <br/> seem a little bit weird, but my questions are provoked by this, it is full of irresponsible parents leading their children after they are in quarantine in the DG. Thus my child suffers, because the constant is limited by contact with children.</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847142_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U17313" RELC_USERNAME="U17313">
<RelCText>In the quarantine of the DG are only contactless smart kids, the rest of your visit)</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847142_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U44643" RELC_USERNAME="U44643">
<RelCText>It's about the kids quarantined from DG, which are displayed, among other children in playgrounds</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847142_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U436333" RELC_USERNAME="U436333">
<RelCText>If the child has been contact with a sick child, it might to be infected those who are past chickenpox may be carriers of the virus. The chance to infect a child for just a minute is 100%-I say this from personal experience-my baby so infect only from HI-HI on playgrounds and I just saw on our playground contagious chicken pox child to play with others and to sow disease Although he was wearing long sleeves. Hate I don't care-stopping it from DK and come on in Parks [smilie = URsmile3511.gif]</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847142_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U17313" RELC_USERNAME="U17313">
<RelCText>[quote author = elpida447 link = topic = 847142. msg30847906 # msg30847906 date = 1432037951] <br/> Once the child has been sick, with contact child-and it can be infected those who are past chickenpox may be carriers of the virus. The chance to infect a child for just a minute is 100%-I say this from personal experience-my baby so infect only from HI-HI on playgrounds and I just saw on our playground contagious chicken pox child to play with others and to plant disease, even though she was wearing long sleeves. Hate I don't care-stopping it from DK and come on in Parks [smilie = URsmile3511.gif] <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/>:p: eace <br/> <br/> Just a clarification-in contact with chickenpox (a person is infected by CA. 2 days before the rash to kill IE still doesn't know he's sick), 9 out of 10 neprekarali the disease is infected. And I and a colleague we under 1%, k. chickenpox repeated them, not as a herpes-zoster, but as a pattern (and both times I was diagnosed by two doctors-the first time by   on duty and personal, I was OK. 20 yy., I had it relatively easy, but it was bad OK. week; the second time, again from the personal, but from pedkata , I was OK. 30 yy., I made it more lightly, as I wasn't feeling well. 2-3 days; both times I kept the House in 10 days, i.e. I didn't infect   sâla:))</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847142_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U44643" RELC_USERNAME="U44643">
<RelCText>And another that interests me if the incubation period (in contact without being informed that the child is in the karantiten period) put the vaccine on the child what could be the consequences?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q847496">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Names" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q847496" RELQ_USERID="U510485" RELQ_USERNAME="U510485">
<RelQSubject>Question for the name Mary</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi, on what name they call a short Buzzing? Often I hear it as obr″ŝanie, but I have no idea. I think it sounds pretty, but I generally love female names with g as Janina and Simi.</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847496_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U325024" RELC_USERNAME="U325024">
<RelCText>Juliet </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847496_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U114738" RELC_USERNAME="U114738">
<RelCText>I have a friend Jasmina, which they say is buzzing, Zhu, Joe. But in putting myself through school classmate Jasmina, had also told that Danny. </RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847496_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U196418" RELC_USERNAME="U196418">
<RelCText>Maybe by Felix. <br/> <br/> Julia, Julia</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847496_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U418381" RELC_USERNAME="U418381">
<RelCText>Maybe the Hollyhock. In general people are creative to caressed names.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q847496_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U510485" RELC_USERNAME="U510485">
<RelCText>And could it be from Simi or Lee?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q848844">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Health care providers, specialists" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q848844" RELQ_USERID="U503253" RELQ_USERNAME="U503253">
<RelQSubject>Questions to the patients of Dr. Darroca</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi! I got a little stupid question: <br/> 1. More Darroca deals with reproductive problems or only with JK and troubled pregnancies. Please girls very important, because I have an appointment soon ... <br/> and if there are girls who have had trouble getting pregnant and have achieved a + result after his intervention to write me:p: ray ray:p::p: ray <br/> <br/></RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q848844_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U491935" RELC_USERNAME="U491935">
<RelCText>Hello! <br/> <br/> depends on what you mean by " reproductive problems " as this is a pretty broad term. As far as I know, he himself is not involved in IVF, but if for example you have lost in early periods of pregnancy it may help you to get rid of them. In any case, it is the most correct your first step to solving your problem, whatever it is, don't forget to get all the documents, medical history reports, photos, advice from previous reviews, abortions (I hope you don't!), if you have any gynecological operations. <br/> <br/> Dr. Darroca will give you a scary accurate assessment of your situation (there's a surefire sense!) and if something falls outside his field of expertise, I will point you to the right specialist. He's brilliant in every respect-ubediŝ alone. Just be prepared to wait and it long. The influx is huge, and he spend a lot of time on each review. <br/> <br/> success!</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q848844_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U359330" RELC_USERNAME="U359330">
<RelCText>Hi girls, please give me information on where I can find Dr. Darroca (hospital or   phone that I could make an appointment)   with three miscarriages from 10 to 14, with one minsrt. As I read about it I feel it will help me. But information where he works after leaving the hospital. Nadeža <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q848844_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U491935" RELC_USERNAME="U491935">
<RelCText>Hello, Maksy! <br/> <br/> Dr. Darroca admit patients in clinic " St. Petka ": <br/> <br/> Sofia, Distr.. Krasno Selo <br/> str. "Gene. Stefan Toshev "No 15-17/at the XX/DKC <br/> Tel: 02/856 79 68 <br/> <br/> http://mc-svetapetka.com/site/? page_id = 123 <br/> <br/> success!</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q848844_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U359330" RELC_USERNAME="U359330">
<RelCText>[quote author = itsybitsy link = topic = 848844. msg31033691 # msg31033691 date = 1434349096] <br/> Hello, Maksy! <br/> <br/> Dr. Darroca admit patients in clinic " St. Petka ": <br/> <br/> Sofia, Distr.. Krasno Selo <br/> str. "Gene. Stefan Toshev "No 15-17/at the XX/DKC <br/> Tel: 02/856 79 68 <br/> <br/> http://mc-svetapetka.com/site/? page_id = 123 <br/> <br/> success! <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> many, many thanks for the comprehensive information  : bouquet:: hug:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q848844_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U28849" RELC_USERNAME="U28849">
<RelCText>I am a patient and looking for the problem. From. I March up to him. Guide to the best excellent specialists, stating research and gives excellent guidelines. And the best part is that vdihva courage, hope and faith that you will succeed. All this with humor and charisma. Go to him, will you help. <br/> success! <br/> Maxi, too. I'm sure they will tell you where the problem is and you will reach a decision. Squeeze your fingers.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q849438">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Health problems" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q849438" RELQ_USERID="U126111" RELQ_USERNAME="U126111">
<RelQSubject>Question about the intake of contraceptive</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi! <br/> Of 5-15 my MC. From that day I started drinking Logest. Yesterday, however, I got a slight spotting, and today's profuse bleeding. I still got a few pills. Today I contacted AG, and told me to pack and doizpiâ under a scheme to start new. <br/> my question is now that I already have a cycle after stopping the pill, you will come to me or to the number for MC?</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q849438_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U62515" RELC_USERNAME="U62515">
<RelCText>What do you have left some pills? It's only been 15 days of your cycle. <br/> <br/> what drink that shit? <br/> in Bulgaria prescribe birth control pills like candy, and they are the reason we're leading in breast cancer in the world statistics:  .</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q849438_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U126111" RELC_USERNAME="U126111">
<RelCText>I drink them primarily to regulate the cycle. Extremely heavy iprod″lžitelen. At a time I couldn't take it anymore and had to take them. Before, I have 4 more pills, and I'm bleeding for three days:?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q849438_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U418096" RELC_USERNAME="U418096">
<RelCText>  Hi! Some time ago and I drank the Logest and the same happened in 2 of the months in the pause was getting not bleeding. The explanation was that since they are very weakly dosed gets this bleeding and need some time to get used to the body. I remember in the leaflet it said, if more than 2 times such bleeding, you need to turn to a doctor likely to prescribe stronger. <br/> PS Each his own decides what and how to drink, so come on, we're criticized, without being aware of.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q849438_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U126111" RELC_USERNAME="U126111">
<RelCText>[b] Nervous User [/b], thank you very much. : hug: <br/> I can probably exchange them with others at the start of the new series? Do you have any observations on some other preparation that eventually won't cause me such discomfort?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q849438_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U418096" RELC_USERNAME="U418096">
<RelCText>  I think it's better to continue with another Pack of these and if you happen to consult a doctor if you change them. It's not good to samonaznačavame  )</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q850907">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Business, work, professions" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q850907" RELQ_USERID="U513147" RELQ_USERNAME="U513147">
<RelQSubject>Revision-question</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi, please advise how to make revision of the kiosk for small food items. I have doubts that the seller a little touch. :( I want 2 consecutive days to count and if something doesn't come up, I will make sure that it is the problem.</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q850907_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U107359" RELC_USERNAME="U107359">
<RelCText><br/> <br/> Than when the seller was appointed to work under an employment contract, i.e. from the first day? <br/> <br/> Upon his appointment, he   with the admission Protocol, is held in Pavilion? <br/> <br/> does anyone else access to the Pavilion and anyone left in the   Pavilion, in the absence of <br/> <br/> seller? <br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q850907_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U513147" RELC_USERNAME="U513147">
<RelCText>Working in shifts, but I have my doubts it is in one. three vendors are. I don't know what's best, with a revision in two consecutive days, after he was a smâns think that will show if INA shortages. ..!? Proposal?</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q850907_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U402339" RELC_USERNAME="U402339">
<RelCText>To do revision two days in a row with a listing of all the small stuff will drive you insane. You must count all night and is still not 100% sure that you will see absolutely everything as it should. I think it is better to find a camera somewhere and to follow him when he's on duty. Without him knowing, of course.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q850907_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U199931" RELC_USERNAME="U199931">
<RelCText>If they shift, so when shortages of the revision pay collectively. Let us make change after his internal audits by peers, so you'd better catch any home for yourself. With a camera would be difficult, especially if there is a serious influx of customers, there's no way to catch whether issued a receipt for all tagged items.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q850907_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U513147" RELC_USERNAME="U513147">
<RelCText>The items are not very ... trudiemko is going to be, but I think it will be worth it. What, exactly, to detect the available in-product sales price, right? I'm not expecting that you will need. Business is not who knows how serious, and I'm not a salesman. But still ...</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q855912">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Problem getting pregnant" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q855912" RELQ_USERID="U250976" RELQ_USERNAME="U250976">
<RelQSubject>About the beginning of the in vitro procedure.</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>My husband and I have a warrant for IVF, we received September 2014 and is valid for 1 year. <br/> we haven't taken advantage of this right. By the end of the period we have about two months to decide. My question is what is taken for the beginning of the process. The commencement of any in vitro procedures, or else the service of order of the physician.</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q855912_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U250538" RELC_USERNAME="U250538">
<RelCText>The start of the stimulation, but I advise you to decide as soon as possible, because you may experience various barriers to the taking-up and drag on it.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q855912_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U488051" RELC_USERNAME="U488051">
<RelCText>I think your time is very nak″sâlo-there are quite a few procedures before the simulations, depending on what the problem is. Whatever   you decide, I wish you success!</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q855912_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U250976" RELC_USERNAME="U250976">
<RelCText>Thanks for the reply. <br/> what you have checked out, just to start. <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q855912_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U365086" RELC_USERNAME="U365086">
<RelCText>The home is believed to be putting the first injection.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q855912_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U423793" RELC_USERNAME="U423793">
<RelCText>You may need to extend the order. Talk to fund what will happen before it's too late.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q856214">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Of time abroad" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q856214" RELQ_USERID="U457808" RELQ_USERNAME="U457808">
<RelQSubject>Prague-questions and tips</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Hi, the only topic related to Prague I found is from eight years ago, and the last answer is six years old, and for this I decided to make another one because I need help. (If there is any current topic, please someone let me write the link.) <br/> <br/> Life &amp; health journey ahead of me soon to Prague, we got tickets booked a hotel, but I have a few questions, because on the Internet I read different things, and in all Sofia could not find a guide to Prague ... <br/> <br/> 1. For public transport we have decided to get a card for 72 hours, is it true that buying slots and can only be done with coins? And also how to proceed?, only Validates the ticket and after (1) It does not validate anywhere? <br/> 2. Mind where can I catch the tram and bus 112 22 are there any stations that stop? <br/> 3. for a boat trip on the River in advance you need to purchase tickets or can spot? <br/> <br/> for now these are the main questions that interest me and I would be very grateful If someone can answer me also if you can recommend any pubs or give me any advice I would be very grateful  : bouquet:</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q856214_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U515418" RELC_USERNAME="U515418">
<RelCText>Sell cards and women at the airport. <br/> <br/> 22 catches from Central Station-Museum, Musteg. Walk around the old centre. There is also a night tram. <br/> <br/> 112 I will get your bearings, there are easy cards. <br/> <br/> Boat shall be paid on the spot, I recommend the jazz boat.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q856214_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U457808" RELC_USERNAME="U457808">
<RelCText>[quote author = The Siren of Titan link = topic = 856214. msg31135124 # msg31135124 date = 1435685138] <br/> sell Cards and women at the airport. <br/> <br/> 22 catches from Central Station-Museum, Musteg. Walk around the old centre. There is also a night tram. <br/> <br/> 112 I will get your bearings, there are easy cards. <br/> <br/> Boat shall be paid on the spot, I recommend the jazz boat. <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> Many thanks  : bouquet:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q856214_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U515418" RELC_USERNAME="U515418">
<RelCText>112 connects to Dejvicka. A large and important station.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q856214_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U283924" RELC_USERNAME="U283924">
<RelCText>Apparatus in subway stations do not remember you, but they were taking notes on the apparatus stops on the tram [b] not [/b] accept banknotes, so, really. Tickets are lasting and are marked on the device (at the entrance to the subway or tram/bus) once and you can switch the vehicles until the end of time. Similarly, I believe that once marked and maps (I haven't used). The Metro is very easily accessible (without roundabouts or self-closing doors), like Berlin. Of the stations there are leaflets with maps and schedules. Trams cover most of Prague, where not enough subway and are very fast. <br/> enjoy traveling around Prague!  :D <br/></RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q856214_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U457808" RELC_USERNAME="U457808">
<RelCText>[quote author = Zaharinka link = topic = 856214. msg31135633 # msg31135633 date = 1435690124] <br/> Apparatus in subway stations do not remember you, but they were taking notes on the apparatus stops on the tram [b] not [/b] accept banknotes, so, really. Tickets are lasting and are marked on the device (at the entrance to the subway or tram/bus) once and you can switch the vehicles until the end of time. Similarly, I believe that once marked and maps (I haven't used). The Metro is very easily accessible (without roundabouts or self-closing doors), like Berlin. Of the stations there are leaflets with maps and schedules. Trams cover most of Prague, where not enough subway and are very fast. <br/> enjoy traveling around Prague!  :D <br/> <br/> [/quote] <br/> <br/> I public transport in Berlin I have bad memories because we bought tickets that we thought are for 24 hours, but it turned out that apply to 12 hours or something   and we had problems with the control  :: crazyeyes <br/> <br/> and for this bus 119, who need to pick up from the airport, you apply the cards and tickets or have a separate ticket?   newsm78</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
<Thread THREAD_SEQUENCE="Q857596">
<RelQuestion RELQ_CATEGORY="Expectant mothers" RELQ_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELQ_ID="Q857596" RELQ_USERID="U516483" RELQ_USERNAME="U516483">
<RelQSubject>question?</RelQSubject>
<RelQBody>Around 6-7 am, and all of a sudden the pain and napregnosta in my chest disappeared. is this normal?</RelQBody>
</RelQuestion>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q857596_C1" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Good" RELC_USERID="U515418" RELC_USERNAME="U515418">
<RelCText>You're more accustomed to discomfort or adapted body. Go for a sonogram to see if implantiralo is OK, then wait. Pregnancy is a very early, abroad to 12 weeks they don't pay attention.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q857596_C2" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U337308" RELC_USERNAME="U337308">
<RelCText>In the future, you can ask your questions in the [url = http://www.bg-mamma.com/index.php? = topicrefid 854030.0; topic = 19] this topic [/url]. :p: eace <br/> <br/> Whether normal is hardly anyone here could say. Every woman, and every pregnancy is different and takes place in a different way with different symptoms. You can discuss these things with doctor who follow pregnancy-he is aware of your condition and his judgment would be much more accurate than ours. To me, all the symptoms disappeared very early and I had a very good and trouble-free pregnancy, but I cannot be a criterion for anyone.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q857596_C3" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U516483" RELC_USERNAME="U516483">
<RelCText>Yesterday I was at the preview. I know it is early pregnancy brain toxin doctor told me after 2 weeks to go again but all of a sudden go away pains me strange and disturbing.</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q857596_C4" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U172093" RELC_USERNAME="U172093">
<RelCText>Go to browse   If something's bothering you. I with the first pregnancy I had no such symptoms at the beginning. Now with the second, TU, Tu subside is mounting. Each pregnancy is different. Good luck and I hope everything and OK!</RelCText>
</RelComment>
<RelComment RELC_DATE="2000-01-01 01:01:01" RELC_ID="Q857596_C5" RELC_RELEVANCE2RELQ="Bad" RELC_USERID="U337308" RELC_USERNAME="U337308">
<RelCText>And to me suddenly disappeared, but I was glad, not worried. <br/> You if you find it disturbing-talk to your doctor. I believe we will manage to calm you down. I wish you success!  : bouquet:</RelCText>
</RelComment>
</Thread>
</xml>